19
00:01:31,841 --> 00:01:37,471
<i>♪ From the day we arrive
on the planet ♪</i>

20
00:01:37,472 --> 00:01:43,310
<i>♪ And, blinking, step into the sun ♪</i>

21
00:01:43,311 --> 00:01:48,732
<i>♪ There's more to see
than can ever be seen ♪</i>

22
00:01:48,733 --> 00:01:54,822
<i>♪ More to do
than can ever be done ♪</i>

23
00:01:54,823 --> 00:01:59,993
<i>♪ There's far too much
to take in here ♪</i>

24
00:01:59,994 --> 00:02:06,333
<i>♪ More to find
than can ever be found ♪</i>

25
00:02:06,334 --> 00:02:08,669
<i>♪ But the sun rolling high ♪</i>

26
00:02:08,670 --> 00:02:11,213
<i>♪ Through the sapphire sky ♪</i>

27
00:02:11,214 --> 00:02:16,301
<i>♪ Keeps great and small
on the endless round ♪</i>

28
00:02:16,302 --> 00:02:21,598
<i>♪ It's the circle of life ♪</i>

29
00:02:21,599 --> 00:02:27,646
<i>♪ And it moves us all ♪</i>

30
00:02:27,647 --> 00:02:33,485
<i>♪ Through despair and hope ♪</i>

31
00:02:33,486 --> 00:02:39,032
<i>♪ Through faith and love ♪</i>

32
00:02:39,159 --> 00:02:44,163
<i>♪ Till we find our place ♪</i>

33
00:02:44,164 --> 00:02:51,503
<i>♪ On the path unwinding ♪</i>

34
00:02:51,504 --> 00:02:56,341
<i>♪ In the circle ♪</i>

35
00:02:56,342 --> 00:03:01,346
<i>♪ The circle of life ♪</i>

36
00:03:48,173 --> 00:03:53,357
<i>♪ It's the circle of life ♪</i>

37
00:03:53,358 --> 00:03:58,904
<i>♪ And it moves us all ♪</i>

38
00:03:58,905 --> 00:04:04,785
<i>♪ Through despair and hope ♪</i>

39
00:04:04,786 --> 00:04:10,457
<i>♪ Through faith and love ♪</i>

40
00:04:10,458 --> 00:04:15,963
<i>♪ Till we find our place ♪</i>

41
00:04:15,964 --> 00:04:22,552
<i>♪ On the path unwinding ♪</i>

42
00:04:22,553 --> 00:04:27,641
<i>♪ In the circle ♪</i>

43
00:04:27,642 --> 00:04:34,288
<i>♪ The circle of life ♪</i>

45
00:04:55,920 --> 00:04:59,260
Life's not fair, is it?

46
00:04:59,261 --> 00:05:03,010
You see, I... Well, I shall never be king.

47
00:05:04,595 --> 00:05:09,516
And you shall never see
the light of another day.

48
00:05:09,517 --> 00:05:10,726
Adieu.

49
00:05:11,644 --> 00:05:14,521
Didn't your mother ever tell you
not to play with your food?

50
00:05:15,106 --> 00:05:16,440
What do you want?

51
00:05:16,524 --> 00:05:17,730
I'm here to announce

52
00:05:17,731 --> 00:05:19,901
that King Mufasa's on his way,

53
00:05:19,986 --> 00:05:22,029
so you'd better have a good excuse

54
00:05:22,030 --> 00:05:23,572
for missing this morning's ceremony.

55
00:05:23,865 --> 00:05:26,616
Oh, look, Zazu.
You've made me lose my lunch.

56
00:05:26,701 --> 00:05:29,619
You'll lose more than that
when the king gets through with you.

57
00:05:29,704 --> 00:05:32,372
He's as mad as a hippo with a hernia.

58
00:05:32,874 --> 00:05:35,917
I quiver with fear!

59
00:05:36,002 --> 00:05:38,545
Now, Scar, don't look at me that way.

60
00:05:38,880 --> 00:05:39,921
Help!

61
00:05:40,256 --> 00:05:42,215
-Scar?
-Mm-hmm?

62
00:05:42,425 --> 00:05:43,467
Drop him.

63
00:05:43,551 --> 00:05:46,803
Impeccable timing, Your Majesty.

64
00:05:49,932 --> 00:05:53,053
Why, if it isn't my big brother

65
00:05:53,054 --> 00:05:56,146
descending from on high
to mingle with the commoners.

66
00:05:56,272 --> 00:05:59,358
Sarabi and I didn't see you
at the presentation of Simba.

67
00:05:59,442 --> 00:06:01,568
That was today?

68
00:06:02,070 --> 00:06:03,987
I feel simply awful!

69
00:06:05,948 --> 00:06:07,949
Must've slipped my mind.

70
00:06:08,076 --> 00:06:11,244
Yes, well, as slippery as your mind is,

71
00:06:11,371 --> 00:06:14,667
as the king's brother,
you should've been first in line!

72
00:06:15,500 --> 00:06:17,319
Well, I was first in line,

73
00:06:17,320 --> 00:06:19,563
until the little hairball was born.

74
00:06:19,564 --> 00:06:22,417
That hairball is my son

75
00:06:22,418 --> 00:06:24,383
and your future king.

76
00:06:24,467 --> 00:06:27,135
I shall practise my curtsy!

77
00:06:27,512 --> 00:06:29,805
Don't turn your back on me, Scar.

78
00:06:29,889 --> 00:06:31,223
Oh, no, Mufasa.

79
00:06:31,307 --> 00:06:34,142
Perhaps you shouldn't
turn your back on me.

80
00:06:35,395 --> 00:06:37,145
Is that a challenge?

81
00:06:37,355 --> 00:06:39,147
Temper, temper.

82
00:06:39,148 --> 00:06:41,983
I wouldn't dream of challenging you.

83
00:06:42,275 --> 00:06:43,985
Pity. Why not?

84
00:06:44,070 --> 00:06:47,786
Well, as far as brains go,
I got the lion's share.

85
00:06:47,787 --> 00:06:50,826
But when it comes to brute strength,

86
00:06:50,910 --> 00:06:55,080
I'm afraid I'm at the shallow end
of the gene pool.

87
00:06:58,251 --> 00:07:00,794
There's one in every family, sire.

88
00:07:00,795 --> 00:07:02,725
Two in mine, actually,

89
00:07:02,726 --> 00:07:05,674
and they always manage to
ruin special occasions.

90
00:07:05,675 --> 00:07:07,342
What am I going to do with him?

91
00:07:07,427 --> 00:07:09,177
He'd make a very handsome throw rug.

92
00:07:09,447 --> 00:07:10,429
Zazu!

93
00:07:10,430 --> 00:07:13,108
And just think,
whenever he gets dirty,

94
00:07:13,109 --> 00:07:15,342
you could take him out and beat him.

95
00:07:54,932 --> 00:07:56,057
Hmm.

96
00:08:00,563 --> 00:08:02,638
Simba.

97
00:08:15,870 --> 00:08:17,262
Dad! Dad!

98
00:08:17,263 --> 00:08:19,581
Come on, dad, we gotta go! Wake up!

99
00:08:20,291 --> 00:08:21,917
-Uhh!
-Sorry.

100
00:08:23,294 --> 00:08:25,378
Dad! Dad!

101
00:08:25,463 --> 00:08:28,340
Your son is awake.

102
00:08:28,424 --> 00:08:31,781
Before sunrise, he's your son.

103
00:08:31,782 --> 00:08:33,678
Dad! Come on, Dad.

104
00:08:38,100 --> 00:08:40,001
You promised.

105
00:08:40,937 --> 00:08:42,812
Okay, Okay.
I'm up, I'm up.

106
00:08:42,939 --> 00:08:43,980
Yeah!

107
00:09:00,289 --> 00:09:01,331
MUFASA: Look, Simba.

108
00:09:01,958 --> 00:09:05,544
Everything the light
touches is our kingdom.

109
00:09:05,628 --> 00:09:07,337
Wow.

110
00:09:07,463 --> 00:09:09,827
A king's time as ruler

111
00:09:09,828 --> 00:09:12,342
rises and falls like the sun.

112
00:09:12,468 --> 00:09:14,155
One day, Simba,

113
00:09:14,156 --> 00:09:16,835
the sun will set on my time here

114
00:09:16,836 --> 00:09:19,891
and will rise with you as the new king.

115
00:09:19,976 --> 00:09:22,686
-And this'll all be mine?
-Everything.

116
00:09:22,770 --> 00:09:25,647
Everything the light touches.

117
00:09:26,357 --> 00:09:28,365
What about that shadowy place?

118
00:09:28,366 --> 00:09:30,110
That's beyond our borders.

119
00:09:30,194 --> 00:09:31,808
You must never go there, Simba.

120
00:09:31,809 --> 00:09:33,822
But I thought a king
can do whatever he wants.

121
00:09:33,823 --> 00:09:35,906
Oh, there's more to being king than...

122
00:09:35,907 --> 00:09:37,381
getting your way all the time.

123
00:09:37,382 --> 00:09:39,578
-There's more?
- Simba...

124
00:09:43,332 --> 00:09:44,887
Everything you see

125
00:09:44,888 --> 00:09:47,752
exists together
in a delicate balance.

126
00:09:47,837 --> 00:09:50,755
As king, you need to
understand that balance

127
00:09:50,840 --> 00:09:52,591
and respect all the creatures,

128
00:09:52,675 --> 00:09:54,292
from the crawling ant

129
00:09:54,293 --> 00:09:55,510
to the leaping antelope.

130
00:09:55,595 --> 00:09:57,555
But, Dad, don't we eat the antelope?

131
00:09:57,556 --> 00:10:00,098
Yes, Simba, but let me explain.

132
00:10:00,308 --> 00:10:03,143
When we die, our bodies
become the grass,

133
00:10:03,436 --> 00:10:05,895
and the antelope eat the grass.

134
00:10:05,980 --> 00:10:09,315
And so we are all connected

135
00:10:09,316 --> 00:10:11,234
in the great circle of life.

136
00:10:11,319 --> 00:10:13,653
-Good morning, sire!
-Good morning, Zazu.

137
00:10:13,654 --> 00:10:15,796
Checking in with the morning report.

138
00:10:15,797 --> 00:10:16,740
Fire away.

139
00:10:16,741 --> 00:10:18,630
Well! The buzz from the bees

140
00:10:18,631 --> 00:10:20,410
is that the leopards
are in a bit of a spot.

141
00:10:20,494 --> 00:10:21,578
Really?

142
00:10:22,893 --> 00:10:23,997
What are you doing, son?

143
00:10:24,838 --> 00:10:25,582
Pouncing.

144
00:10:25,666 --> 00:10:28,201
Let an old pro show you how it's done.

145
00:10:28,294 --> 00:10:31,087
I told the elephants to forget it,
but they can't...

146
00:10:31,172 --> 00:10:33,220
-Zazu, would you turn around?
-Yes, sire.

147
00:10:33,221 --> 00:10:35,842
- The cheetahs are hard up, but...
- Stay low to the ground.

148
00:10:36,010 --> 00:10:38,096
- Cheetahs never prosper...
- Yeah, okay.

149
00:10:38,097 --> 00:10:39,429
Stay low to the ground, right? Yeah.

150
00:10:39,513 --> 00:10:40,680
-What going on?
-A pouncing lesson.

151
00:10:40,806 --> 00:10:43,016
Very good. Pouncing.

152
00:10:43,100 --> 00:10:46,519
Pouncing?
No, sire, you can't be serious...

153
00:10:47,521 --> 00:10:49,550
This is so humiliating.

154
00:10:49,551 --> 00:10:50,940
Try not to make a sound.

155
00:10:51,025 --> 00:10:53,318
What are you telling him, Mufasa?

156
00:10:53,986 --> 00:10:56,655
Mufasa? Simba?

157
00:11:00,534 --> 00:11:01,701
That's very good.

158
00:11:02,370 --> 00:11:03,320
-Zazu!
-Yes!

159
00:11:03,321 --> 00:11:04,974
Sir! News from the underground.

160
00:11:04,975 --> 00:11:06,373
Now, this time...

161
00:11:06,457 --> 00:11:09,709
Sire! Hyenas in the Pride Lands!

162
00:11:09,835 --> 00:11:11,378
Zazu, take Simba home.

163
00:11:11,379 --> 00:11:12,629
Aw, dad, can't I come?

164
00:11:12,630 --> 00:11:13,713
No, son.

165
00:11:14,799 --> 00:11:17,311
Pah! I never get to go anywhere.

166
00:11:17,312 --> 00:11:18,972
Oh, young master,

167
00:11:18,973 --> 00:11:21,352
one day, you will be king.

168
00:11:21,353 --> 00:11:22,488
Then you can chase

169
00:11:22,489 --> 00:11:25,389
those slobbering, mangy,
stupid poachers

170
00:11:25,390 --> 00:11:27,227
from dawn until dusk.

171
00:11:34,318 --> 00:11:37,144
Hey, Uncle Scar!
Guess what?

172
00:11:37,145 --> 00:11:39,823
I despise guessing games.

173
00:11:39,907 --> 00:11:41,991
I'm gonna be King of Pride Rock.

174
00:11:42,076 --> 00:11:44,327
Oh, goody!

175
00:11:44,412 --> 00:11:46,162
My dad just showed me
the whole kingdom,

176
00:11:46,247 --> 00:11:49,249
and I'm gonna rule it all!

177
00:11:49,375 --> 00:11:53,271
Yes. Well, forgive me
for not leaping for joy.

178
00:11:53,272 --> 00:11:55,255
Bad back, you know.

179
00:11:56,257 --> 00:11:57,424
Hey, Uncle Scar.

180
00:11:57,508 --> 00:12:00,088
When I'm king,
what'll that make you?

181
00:12:00,089 --> 00:12:02,178
A monkey's uncle.

182
00:12:02,263 --> 00:12:04,076
You're so weird.

183
00:12:04,077 --> 00:12:06,099
You have no idea.

184
00:12:06,183 --> 00:12:09,826
So, your father showed you
the whole kingdom, did he?

185
00:12:09,827 --> 00:12:10,520
Everything.

186
00:12:10,604 --> 00:12:14,190
He didn't show you what's beyond
that rise at the northern border?

187
00:12:14,567 --> 00:12:17,694
Well, no. He said I can't go there.

188
00:12:17,778 --> 00:12:19,779
And he's absolutely right.

189
00:12:19,905 --> 00:12:21,546
It's far too dangerous.

190
00:12:21,547 --> 00:12:23,700
Only the bravest lions go there.

191
00:12:23,784 --> 00:12:26,453
Well, I'm brave. What's out there?

192
00:12:26,579 --> 00:12:29,038
I'm sorry, Simba,
I just can't tell you.

193
00:12:29,039 --> 00:12:29,880
Why not?

194
00:12:29,881 --> 00:12:31,203
Simba, Simba,

195
00:12:31,204 --> 00:12:34,627
I'm only looking out for the
well-being of my favourite nephew.

196
00:12:34,754 --> 00:12:37,547
Yeah, right! I'm your only nephew.

197
00:12:37,631 --> 00:12:40,133
All the more reason
for me to be protective.

198
00:12:40,426 --> 00:12:42,044
An elephant graveyard

199
00:12:42,045 --> 00:12:44,471
is no place
for a young prince. Oops!

200
00:12:44,764 --> 00:12:47,140
An elephant what? Whoa!

201
00:12:47,308 --> 00:12:50,393
Oh, dear, I've said too much.

202
00:12:50,478 --> 00:12:53,313
Well, I suppose you'd have
found out sooner or later,

203
00:12:53,481 --> 00:12:56,399
you being so clever and all.

204
00:12:56,484 --> 00:12:58,151
Just do me one favour.

205
00:12:58,277 --> 00:13:02,822
Promise me you'll never visit
that dreadful place.

206
00:13:02,948 --> 00:13:04,324
No problem.

207
00:13:04,450 --> 00:13:06,075
There's a good lad.

208
00:13:06,160 --> 00:13:08,912
You run along now and have fun.

209
00:13:08,996 --> 00:13:10,497
And remember,

210
00:13:10,581 --> 00:13:13,082
it's our little secret.

211
00:13:20,508 --> 00:13:22,175
-Hey, Nala.
-Hi, Simba.

212
00:13:22,301 --> 00:13:24,427
Come on. I just heard
about this great place.

213
00:13:24,512 --> 00:13:27,013
Simba! I'm kind of
in the middle of a bath.

214
00:13:27,139 --> 00:13:29,182
SARABI: And it's time for yours.

215
00:13:30,518 --> 00:13:32,268
Mom!

216
00:13:32,353 --> 00:13:35,271
Mom, you're messing up my mane!

217
00:13:36,607 --> 00:13:39,108
Okay, okay, I'm clean.
Can we go now?

218
00:13:39,193 --> 00:13:40,527
So, where are we going?

219
00:13:40,611 --> 00:13:42,111
It better not be anyplace dumb.

220
00:13:42,196 --> 00:13:44,155
No, it's really cool.

221
00:13:44,156 --> 00:13:46,616
So, where is this really cool place?

222
00:13:46,700 --> 00:13:48,117
Oh.

223
00:13:48,202 --> 00:13:50,870
-Uh, around the water hole.
-The water hole?

224
00:13:50,996 --> 00:13:52,789
What's so great about the water hole?

225
00:13:52,873 --> 00:13:55,041
I'll show you when we get there.

226
00:13:55,125 --> 00:13:56,292
Oh.

227
00:13:56,377 --> 00:13:58,211
Uh, mom, can I go with Simba?

228
00:13:58,629 --> 00:14:00,547
Hmm, what do you think, Sarabi?

229
00:14:00,631 --> 00:14:01,673
Well...

230
00:14:01,882 --> 00:14:03,132
BOTH: Please?

231
00:14:03,217 --> 00:14:04,384
It's all right with me.

232
00:14:04,468 --> 00:14:05,552
-Yeah!
-All right!

233
00:14:05,636 --> 00:14:07,554
As long as Zazu goes with you.

234
00:14:07,638 --> 00:14:09,222
No, not Zazu.

235
00:14:09,807 --> 00:14:10,807
ZAZU: Step lively.

236
00:14:10,891 --> 00:14:12,529
The sooner we get to the water hole,

237
00:14:12,530 --> 00:14:14,894
the sooner we can leave.

238
00:14:14,979 --> 00:14:16,855
So, where are we really going?

239
00:14:16,981 --> 00:14:18,314
An elephant graveyard.

240
00:14:18,399 --> 00:14:19,399
Wow!

241
00:14:19,525 --> 00:14:20,984
Shh! Zazu.

242
00:14:21,068 --> 00:14:23,820
Right. So, how are we
gonna ditch the dodo?

243
00:14:24,655 --> 00:14:26,739
Oh, just look at you two.

244
00:14:26,824 --> 00:14:29,909
Little seeds of romance
blossoming in the savanna.

245
00:14:30,035 --> 00:14:32,245
Your parents will be thrilled,

246
00:14:32,371 --> 00:14:34,956
what with your being betrothed and all.

247
00:14:34,957 --> 00:14:35,722
Be-what?

248
00:14:35,723 --> 00:14:37,584
Betrothed. Intended.

249
00:14:37,751 --> 00:14:39,586
Affianced.

250
00:14:39,712 --> 00:14:40,753
Meaning...

251
00:14:40,921 --> 00:14:43,840
One day, you two are
going to be married.

252
00:14:43,924 --> 00:14:44,924
-Yuck!
-Eww!

253
00:14:45,050 --> 00:14:47,389
I can't marry her.
She's my friend.

254
00:14:47,390 --> 00:14:49,512
Yeah, it'd be so weird.

255
00:14:49,597 --> 00:14:51,726
Sorry to bust your bubble,

256
00:14:51,727 --> 00:14:54,516
but you two turtle doves
have no choice.

257
00:14:54,517 --> 00:14:56,769
It's a tradition going back generations.

258
00:14:56,896 --> 00:14:59,397
When I'm king,
that'll be the first thing to go.

259
00:14:59,481 --> 00:15:02,317
-Not so long as I'm around.
-Well, in that case, you're fired.

260
00:15:02,443 --> 00:15:04,944
Nice try, but only the king can do that.

261
00:15:04,945 --> 00:15:06,487
Well, he's the future king.

262
00:15:06,614 --> 00:15:08,948
Yeah, so you have to do what I tell you.

263
00:15:09,116 --> 00:15:10,491
Not yet, I don't.

264
00:15:10,618 --> 00:15:12,186
And with an attitude like that,

265
00:15:12,187 --> 00:15:15,914
I'm afraid you're shaping up to be
a pretty pathetic king, indeed.

266
00:15:15,998 --> 00:15:17,624
Not the way I see it.

267
00:15:18,417 --> 00:15:21,106
<i>♪ I'm gonna be a mighty king ♪</i>

268
00:15:21,107 --> 00:15:22,921
<i>♪ So enemies beware ♪</i>

269
00:15:23,005 --> 00:15:25,590
<i>♪ Well, I've never seen
a king of beasts ♪</i>

270
00:15:25,674 --> 00:15:27,842
<i>♪ With quite so little hair ♪</i>

271
00:15:27,968 --> 00:15:30,553
<i>♪ I'm gonna be the main event ♪</i>

272
00:15:30,638 --> 00:15:32,680
<i>♪ Like no king was before ♪</i>

273
00:15:33,015 --> 00:15:35,391
<i>♪ I'm brushin' up on lookin' down ♪</i>

274
00:15:35,476 --> 00:15:37,602
<i>♪ I'm workin' on my roar ♪</i>

275
00:15:37,686 --> 00:15:41,314
<i>♪ Thus far, a rather uninspiring thing ♪</i>

276
00:15:41,941 --> 00:15:46,587
<i>♪ Oh, I just can't wait to be king ♪</i>

277
00:15:46,588 --> 00:15:49,530
You've rather a long way to go,
young master, if you think...

278
00:15:49,657 --> 00:15:52,033
-No one sayin', "Do this"
-Now, when I said that...

279
00:15:52,034 --> 00:15:54,535
-No one saying, "Be there"
-What I meant was...

280
00:15:54,536 --> 00:15:56,996
-No one sayin', "Stop that"
-You don't realise...

281
00:15:56,997 --> 00:15:59,791
-No one sayin', "See here"
-Now, see here!

282
00:15:59,875 --> 00:16:03,211
<i>♪ Free to run around all day ♪</i>

283
00:16:03,337 --> 00:16:04,879
Well, that's definitely out.

284
00:16:05,005 --> 00:16:09,008
<i>♪ Free to do it all my way ♪</i>

285
00:16:11,845 --> 00:16:14,305
<i>♪ I think it's time that you and I ♪</i>

286
00:16:14,390 --> 00:16:16,474
<i>♪ Arranged a heart-to-heart ♪</i>

287
00:16:16,809 --> 00:16:18,562
<i>♪ Kings don't need advice ♪</i>

288
00:16:18,563 --> 00:16:20,979
<i>♪ From little hornbills for a start ♪</i>

289
00:16:21,647 --> 00:16:25,008
<i>♪ If this is where
the monarchy is headed ♪</i>

290
00:16:25,009 --> 00:16:26,211
<i>♪ Count me out ♪</i>

291
00:16:26,212 --> 00:16:28,319
<i>♪ Out of service, out of Africa ♪</i>

292
00:16:28,404 --> 00:16:30,989
<i>♪ I wouldn't hang about ♪</i>

293
00:16:31,657 --> 00:16:35,368
<i>♪ This child is getting
wildly out of wing ♪</i>

294
00:16:35,965 --> 00:16:39,914
<i>♪ Oh, I just can't wait to be king ♪</i>

295
00:16:52,511 --> 00:16:54,220
<i>♪ Everybody, look left ♪</i>

296
00:16:55,180 --> 00:16:57,800
<i>♪ Everybody, look right ♪</i>

297
00:16:57,801 --> 00:17:00,051
<i>♪ Everywhere you look, I'm ♪</i>

298
00:17:00,052 --> 00:17:01,949
<i>♪ Standing in the spotlight ♪</i>

299
00:17:01,950 --> 00:17:02,985
Not yet!

300
00:17:02,986 --> 00:17:07,066
<i>♪ Let every creature
go for broke and sing ♪</i>

301
00:17:07,768 --> 00:17:11,229
<i>♪ Let's hear it in the herd
and on the wing ♪</i>

302
00:17:12,773 --> 00:17:16,901
<i>♪ It's gonna be
King Simba's finest fling ♪</i>

303
00:17:16,985 --> 00:17:26,827
Oh, I just can't wait to be king

304
00:17:26,954 --> 00:17:33,000
Oh, I just can't wait

305
00:17:33,001 --> 00:17:35,127
To be king

306
00:17:41,143 --> 00:17:44,262
ZAZU:
I beg your pardon, madam, but

307
00:17:44,263 --> 00:17:46,138
get off!

308
00:17:46,640 --> 00:17:48,207
Simba?

309
00:17:48,208 --> 00:17:50,142
Nala!

310
00:17:52,604 --> 00:17:53,896
All right! It worked!

311
00:17:53,981 --> 00:17:56,857
-We lost him.
-I am a genius.

312
00:17:56,858 --> 00:17:58,693
Hey, genius, it was my idea.

313
00:17:58,694 --> 00:18:00,861
Yeah, but I pulled it off.

314
00:18:00,988 --> 00:18:02,947
-With me!
-Oh, yeah?

315
00:18:06,118 --> 00:18:09,203
-Pinned ya.
-Hey, let me up!

316
00:18:14,001 --> 00:18:16,127
Pinned ya again.

317
00:18:28,390 --> 00:18:30,850
This is it. We made it.

318
00:18:35,063 --> 00:18:36,647
Whoa!

319
00:18:39,318 --> 00:18:41,027
NALA: It's really creepy.

320
00:18:41,153 --> 00:18:42,194
Yeah.

321
00:18:42,321 --> 00:18:43,529
Isn't it great?

322
00:18:43,655 --> 00:18:46,741
-We could get in big trouble.
-I know!

323
00:18:47,200 --> 00:18:49,952
I wonder if its brains are still in there.

324
00:18:50,037 --> 00:18:51,912
There's only one way to know.

325
00:18:52,039 --> 00:18:53,622
Come on, let's go check it out.

326
00:18:53,623 --> 00:18:57,878
Wrong! The only checking out you
will do will be to check out of here.

327
00:18:57,879 --> 00:18:58,636
Oh, man!

328
00:18:58,637 --> 00:19:01,422
We're way beyond the boundary
of the Pride Lands.

329
00:19:01,590 --> 00:19:03,132
Look, banana beak is scared.

330
00:19:03,216 --> 00:19:06,213
It's Mr banana beak to you, fuzzy,

331
00:19:06,214 --> 00:19:09,513
and right now we are all
in very real danger.

332
00:19:09,598 --> 00:19:11,015
Danger? Ha!

333
00:19:11,099 --> 00:19:13,184
I walk on the wild side.

334
00:19:13,268 --> 00:19:15,519
I laugh in the face of danger.

335
00:19:15,771 --> 00:19:17,021
Ha ha ha ha!

336
00:19:24,404 --> 00:19:27,615
Well, well, well, Banzai,
what have we got here?

337
00:19:27,741 --> 00:19:29,617
I don't know, Shenzi.

338
00:19:30,410 --> 00:19:32,036
What do you think, Ed?

339
00:19:34,331 --> 00:19:36,082
Just what I was thinking.

340
00:19:36,625 --> 00:19:38,167
A trio of trespassers!

341
00:19:38,251 --> 00:19:40,586
And quite by accident,
let me assure you.

342
00:19:40,587 --> 00:19:42,380
A simple navigational error.

343
00:19:42,464 --> 00:19:44,423
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.

344
00:19:44,508 --> 00:19:48,511
I know you.
You're Mufasa's little stooge.

345
00:19:48,595 --> 00:19:50,888
I, madam, am the king's major-domo.

346
00:19:50,972 --> 00:19:52,737
And that would make you...

347
00:19:52,738 --> 00:19:54,088
The future king.

348
00:19:54,089 --> 00:19:57,645
Do you know what we do to kings
who step out of their kingdom?

349
00:19:57,854 --> 00:20:00,439
Huh! You can't do anything to me.

350
00:20:00,524 --> 00:20:02,780
Technically, they can.
We are on their land.

351
00:20:02,781 --> 00:20:07,071
But Zazu, you told me they're nothing but
slobbering, mangy, stupid poachers.

352
00:20:07,155 --> 00:20:09,050
Ix-nay on the upid-stay.

353
00:20:09,051 --> 00:20:11,909
-Who are you callin' upid-stay?
-My, my, my. Oh, look at the sun!

354
00:20:11,993 --> 00:20:14,086
-It's time to go!
-What's the hurry?

355
00:20:14,087 --> 00:20:16,080
We'd love you to
stick around for dinner.

356
00:20:16,164 --> 00:20:19,938
Yeah, we could have
whatever's lion around!

357
00:20:19,939 --> 00:20:21,585
Wait, wait, wait, I got one, I got one!

358
00:20:21,670 --> 00:20:24,997
Make mine a cub sandwich!
Whaddaya think?

359
00:20:26,550 --> 00:20:28,968
What, Ed? What is it?

360
00:20:29,052 --> 00:20:30,886
Hey, did we order this dinner to go?

361
00:20:31,012 --> 00:20:32,054
No, why?

362
00:20:32,180 --> 00:20:34,306
'Cause there it goes!

363
00:20:40,522 --> 00:20:43,232
-Did we lose 'em?
-I think so.

364
00:20:43,358 --> 00:20:44,733
Where's Zazu?

365
00:20:44,860 --> 00:20:46,695
The little major-domo bird

366
00:20:46,696 --> 00:20:49,071
hippety-hopped all the way
to the birdie-boiler.

367
00:20:49,531 --> 00:20:52,199
Oh, no! Not the birdie-boiler!

368
00:20:52,325 --> 00:20:54,243
Aaaah!

369
00:20:55,537 --> 00:20:58,831
Hey, why don't you pick
on somebody your own size?

370
00:20:59,040 --> 00:21:01,333
-Like you?
-Oops.

371
00:21:03,253 --> 00:21:05,504
Boo!

372
00:21:17,601 --> 00:21:19,518
NALA: Simba!

373
00:21:37,579 --> 00:21:41,040
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.

374
00:21:45,545 --> 00:21:46,879
That was it?

375
00:21:47,464 --> 00:21:49,256
Do it again. Come on.

376
00:22:01,069 --> 00:22:03,034
- Oh, please, please!
- Uncle, uncle!

377
00:22:03,035 --> 00:22:03,729
Silence!

378
00:22:03,813 --> 00:22:07,024
-We're gonna shut up right now!
-Calm down. We're really sorry.

379
00:22:07,108 --> 00:22:10,236
If you ever come near my son again...

380
00:22:10,487 --> 00:22:11,987
Oh, this is... This is your son?

381
00:22:12,072 --> 00:22:14,573
-Oh, your son.
-Did you know that?

382
00:22:14,658 --> 00:22:17,076
No. Me? I didn't know...
No, did you?

383
00:22:17,160 --> 00:22:19,078
-No, of course not.
-No.

384
00:22:19,162 --> 00:22:20,246
Ed?

385
00:22:23,583 --> 00:22:24,917
Toodles.

386
00:22:32,175 --> 00:22:34,727
-Dad, I...
-You deliberately disobeyed me.

387
00:22:36,263 --> 00:22:39,181
-Dad, I'm... I'm sorry.
-Let's go home.

388
00:22:42,269 --> 00:22:44,812
I thought you were very brave.

389
00:23:01,538 --> 00:23:03,038
MUFASA: Zazu.

390
00:23:05,125 --> 00:23:07,562
- Yes, sire?
- Take Nala home.

391
00:23:07,563 --> 00:23:10,671
I've got to teach my son a lesson.

392
00:23:14,884 --> 00:23:16,802
Come, Nala.

393
00:23:16,886 --> 00:23:18,970
Simba,

394
00:23:18,971 --> 00:23:20,306
good luck.

395
00:23:25,979 --> 00:23:27,980
Simba!

396
00:23:55,592 --> 00:23:57,509
Simba, I'm very disappointed in you.

397
00:23:57,594 --> 00:24:00,012
-I know.
-You could've been killed.

398
00:24:00,096 --> 00:24:01,995
You deliberately disobeyed me,

399
00:24:01,996 --> 00:24:05,893
and what's worse,
you put Nala in danger.

400
00:24:06,094 --> 00:24:08,562
I was just trying to be brave, like you.

401
00:24:09,022 --> 00:24:12,024
I'm only brave when I have to be.

402
00:24:12,108 --> 00:24:15,736
Simba, being brave

403
00:24:15,820 --> 00:24:18,155
doesn't mean you go
looking for trouble.

404
00:24:18,281 --> 00:24:20,282
But you're not scared of anything.

405
00:24:21,451 --> 00:24:22,576
I was today.

406
00:24:22,661 --> 00:24:24,828
-You were?
-Yes.

407
00:24:24,954 --> 00:24:27,039
I thought I might lose you.

408
00:24:27,123 --> 00:24:31,126
I guess even kings get scared, huh?

409
00:24:31,211 --> 00:24:32,378
Mm-hmm.

410
00:24:32,462 --> 00:24:34,713
-But you know what?
-What?

411
00:24:34,798 --> 00:24:37,341
I think those hyenas
were even scareder.

412
00:24:38,968 --> 00:24:42,096
'Cause nobody messes with your dad.

413
00:24:42,180 --> 00:24:44,640
-Come here, you.
-Oh, no! No!

414
00:24:44,808 --> 00:24:47,059
Aagh! Uhh!

415
00:24:47,427 --> 00:24:49,353
SIMBA: Come here!

416
00:24:50,730 --> 00:24:51,897
Gotcha!

417
00:24:57,153 --> 00:24:58,696
-Dad?
-Hmm?

418
00:24:58,822 --> 00:25:00,563
We're pals, right?

419
00:25:00,564 --> 00:25:01,657
Right.

420
00:25:01,658 --> 00:25:04,368
And we'll always be together, right?

421
00:25:05,662 --> 00:25:07,315
Simba,

422
00:25:07,316 --> 00:25:11,375
let me tell you something
that my father told me.

423
00:25:11,501 --> 00:25:13,752
Look at the stars.

424
00:25:13,753 --> 00:25:16,051
The great kings of the past

425
00:25:16,052 --> 00:25:18,549
look down on us from those stars.

426
00:25:18,913 --> 00:25:20,926
-Really?
-Yes.

427
00:25:21,010 --> 00:25:23,387
So whenever you feel alone,

428
00:25:23,388 --> 00:25:28,142
just remember that those kings
will always be there to guide you.

429
00:25:29,602 --> 00:25:31,478
And so will I.

430
00:25:38,236 --> 00:25:39,890
BANZAI: Man, that lousy Mufasa.

431
00:25:39,891 --> 00:25:41,864
I won't be able to sit for a week.

432
00:25:45,076 --> 00:25:46,702
It's not funny, Ed.

433
00:25:50,540 --> 00:25:52,708
Hey, shut up!

434
00:25:55,545 --> 00:25:57,171
Will you knock it off?

435
00:25:58,381 --> 00:25:59,582
Well, he started it.

436
00:25:59,988 --> 00:26:01,383
SHENZI: Look at you guys.

437
00:26:01,634 --> 00:26:04,052
No wonder we're dangling
at the bottom of the food chain.

438
00:26:04,179 --> 00:26:05,286
Man, I hate dangling.

439
00:26:05,287 --> 00:26:08,154
Yeah? If it weren't for those lions,

440
00:26:08,155 --> 00:26:09,558
we'd be runnin' the joint.

441
00:26:09,684 --> 00:26:11,059
Man, I hate lions.

442
00:26:11,186 --> 00:26:12,811
-So pushy.
-And hairy.

443
00:26:12,896 --> 00:26:14,980
-And stinky.
-And, man, are they...

444
00:26:15,064 --> 00:26:17,065
BOTH: Ugly!

445
00:26:18,485 --> 00:26:22,237
Oh, surely we lions are not all that bad.

446
00:26:22,614 --> 00:26:25,612
-Oh.
-Oh, Scar. It's just you.

447
00:26:25,613 --> 00:26:27,326
We were afraid it was
somebody important.

448
00:26:27,410 --> 00:26:28,827
Yeah, you know, like Mufasa.

449
00:26:28,912 --> 00:26:30,454
-SHENZI: Yeah.
-I see.

450
00:26:30,538 --> 00:26:32,831
-Now that's power!
-Tell me about it.

451
00:26:32,916 --> 00:26:34,666
I just hear that name and I shudder.

452
00:26:34,751 --> 00:26:37,336
-Mufasa!
-Ooh! Do it again.

453
00:26:37,420 --> 00:26:38,754
-Mufasa!
-Ooooh!

454
00:26:39,128 --> 00:26:41,423
Mufasa! Mufasa! Mufasa!

455
00:26:42,133 --> 00:26:43,300
SHENZI: Ooh, it tingles me.

456
00:26:43,384 --> 00:26:46,261
I'm surrounded by idiots.

457
00:26:46,346 --> 00:26:48,241
Now, you, Scar,
I mean, you're one of us.

458
00:26:48,242 --> 00:26:49,431
I mean, you're our pal.

459
00:26:49,557 --> 00:26:50,516
Charmed.

460
00:26:50,767 --> 00:26:52,053
Oh, I like that.

461
00:26:52,054 --> 00:26:55,094
He's not king,
but he's still so proper.

462
00:26:55,095 --> 00:26:57,002
Yeah. Hey, did you
bring us anything to eat,

463
00:26:57,003 --> 00:26:59,107
Scar, old buddy, old pal?
Huh? Did ya, did ya, did ya?

464
00:26:59,108 --> 00:27:01,443
I don't think you really deserve this.

465
00:27:01,569 --> 00:27:04,613
I practically gift-wrapped
those cubs for you,

466
00:27:04,739 --> 00:27:08,116
and you couldn't even dispose of them.

467
00:27:10,787 --> 00:27:11,949
Well, you know,

468
00:27:11,950 --> 00:27:14,873
it wasn't exactly
like they was alone, Scar.

469
00:27:14,958 --> 00:27:17,125
Yeah. What were we supposed to do?

470
00:27:17,627 --> 00:27:19,127
Kill Mufasa?

471
00:27:20,880 --> 00:27:22,798
Precisely.

472
00:27:33,226 --> 00:27:37,145
<i>♪ l know that your powers
of retention ♪</i>

473
00:27:37,272 --> 00:27:40,983
<i>♪ Are as wet as a warthog's backside ♪</i>

474
00:27:41,109 --> 00:27:43,213
<i>♪ But thick as you are ♪</i>

475
00:27:43,214 --> 00:27:45,237
<i>♪ Pay attention ♪</i>

476
00:27:45,321 --> 00:27:49,074
<i>♪ My words are a matter of pride ♪</i>

477
00:27:49,158 --> 00:27:52,828
<i>♪ It's clear from your vacant expressions ♪</i>

478
00:27:52,954 --> 00:27:56,832
<i>♪ The lights are not all on upstairs ♪</i>

479
00:27:56,958 --> 00:28:00,335
<i>♪ But we're talking kings
and successions ♪</i>

480
00:28:00,461 --> 00:28:03,171
<i>♪ Even you can't be caught unawares ♪</i>

481
00:28:04,591 --> 00:28:08,176
<i>♪ So prepare for the chance of a lifetime ♪</i>

482
00:28:08,261 --> 00:28:12,639
<i>♪ Be prepared for sensational news ♪</i>

483
00:28:12,724 --> 00:28:16,560
<i>♪ A shiny new era is tiptoeing nearer ♪</i>

484
00:28:16,644 --> 00:28:18,228
<i>♪ And where do we feature? ♪</i>

485
00:28:18,313 --> 00:28:20,522
<i>♪ Just listen to teacher ♪</i>

486
00:28:20,607 --> 00:28:22,482
<i>♪ I know it sounds sordid ♪</i>

487
00:28:22,567 --> 00:28:24,443
<i>♪ But you'll be rewarded ♪</i>

488
00:28:24,527 --> 00:28:28,071
<i>♪ When at last I am given my dues ♪</i>

489
00:28:28,156 --> 00:28:31,700
<i>♪ And injustice deliciously squared ♪</i>

490
00:28:31,784 --> 00:28:34,995
<i>♪ Be prepared ♪</i>

491
00:28:35,079 --> 00:28:38,409
Yeah, be prepared.
We'll be prepared.

492
00:28:38,410 --> 00:28:39,049
For what?

493
00:28:39,050 --> 00:28:40,542
For the death of the king.

494
00:28:40,627 --> 00:28:43,386
-Why, is he sick?
-No, fool, we're going to kill him.

495
00:28:43,387 --> 00:28:44,615
And Simba, too.

496
00:28:44,616 --> 00:28:46,506
Great idea. Who needs a king?

497
00:28:46,591 --> 00:28:49,268
<i>♪ No king, no king, la-la la-la la la ♪</i>

498
00:28:49,269 --> 00:28:51,490
Idiots! There will be a king!

499
00:28:51,491 --> 00:28:54,874
- Hey, but you said...
- I will be king!

500
00:28:54,875 --> 00:28:56,350
Stick with me,

501
00:28:56,434 --> 00:29:00,354
and you'll never go hungry again.

502
00:29:00,438 --> 00:29:03,140
-Yeah! All right!
-Long live the king!

503
00:29:03,141 --> 00:29:06,276
Long live the king! Long live the king!

504
00:29:08,196 --> 00:29:11,448
<i>♪ It's great that we'll soon be connected ♪</i>

505
00:29:11,532 --> 00:29:15,711
<i>♪ With a king who'll be all-time adored ♪</i>

506
00:29:15,712 --> 00:29:19,626
<i>♪ Of course, quid pro quo
you're expected ♪</i>

507
00:29:19,627 --> 00:29:23,460
<i>♪ To take certain duties on board ♪</i>

508
00:29:23,586 --> 00:29:27,297
<i>♪ The future is littered with prizes ♪</i>

509
00:29:27,423 --> 00:29:31,802
<i>♪ And though I'm the main addressee ♪</i>

510
00:29:31,886 --> 00:29:35,222
<i>♪ The point that I must emphasise is ♪</i>

511
00:29:35,306 --> 00:29:38,225
<i>♪ You won't get a sniff without me! ♪</i>

512
00:29:39,143 --> 00:29:42,729
<i>♪ So prepare for the coup of the century ♪</i>

513
00:29:42,814 --> 00:29:47,150
<i>♪ Be prepared for the murkiest scam ♪</i>

514
00:29:47,276 --> 00:29:48,902
<i>♪ Meticulous planning ♪</i>

515
00:29:48,987 --> 00:29:50,904
<i>♪ Tenacity spanning ♪</i>

516
00:29:50,989 --> 00:29:53,073
<i>♪ Decades of denial ♪</i>

517
00:29:53,157 --> 00:29:56,827
<i>♪ Is simply why I'll be king undisputed ♪</i>

518
00:29:56,911 --> 00:29:58,829
<i>♪ Respected, saluted ♪</i>

519
00:29:58,955 --> 00:30:02,332
<i>♪ And seen for the wonder I am ♪</i>

520
00:30:02,458 --> 00:30:06,169
<i>♪ Yes, my teeth and ambitions are bared ♪</i>

521
00:30:06,295 --> 00:30:09,506
<i>♪ Be prepared ♪</i>

522
00:30:10,675 --> 00:30:14,011
<i>♪ Yes, our teeth and ambitions are bared ♪</i>

523
00:30:14,095 --> 00:30:18,015
<i>♪ Be prepared ♪</i>

524
00:30:30,486 --> 00:30:34,948
SCAR: You wait here. Your father has
a marvellous surprise for you.

525
00:30:35,033 --> 00:30:36,283
Ooh, what is it?

526
00:30:36,367 --> 00:30:39,578
If I told you, it wouldn't be
a surprise now, would it?

527
00:30:39,704 --> 00:30:41,839
If you tell me,
I'll still act surprised.

528
00:30:41,840 --> 00:30:45,625
Ho ho ho!
You are such a naughty boy.

529
00:30:45,710 --> 00:30:47,278
Come on, Uncle Scar.

530
00:30:47,279 --> 00:30:48,837
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.

531
00:30:48,921 --> 00:30:51,256
This is just for you and your daddy.

532
00:30:51,382 --> 00:30:56,011
You know, a sort of father-son thing.

533
00:30:56,095 --> 00:30:58,889
Well, I'd better go get him.

534
00:30:59,015 --> 00:31:00,807
-I'll go with you.
-No.

535
00:31:02,268 --> 00:31:06,021
No. Just stay on this rock.

536
00:31:06,105 --> 00:31:08,106
You wouldn't want to end up
in another mess

537
00:31:08,232 --> 00:31:09,900
like you did with the hyenas.

538
00:31:10,068 --> 00:31:11,368
You know about that?

539
00:31:11,369 --> 00:31:13,904
Simba, everybody knows about that.

540
00:31:13,988 --> 00:31:16,573
-Really?
-Oh, yes.

541
00:31:16,657 --> 00:31:20,368
Lucky daddy was there
to save you, eh?

542
00:31:20,453 --> 00:31:23,163
Oh, and just between us,

543
00:31:23,247 --> 00:31:26,625
you might want to work on
that little roar of yours, hmm?

544
00:31:27,001 --> 00:31:28,627
Oh. Okay.

545
00:31:31,297 --> 00:31:34,925
Hey, Uncle Scar,
will I like this surprise?

546
00:31:35,301 --> 00:31:39,004
Simba, it's to die for.

547
00:32:00,576 --> 00:32:01,993
Shut up.

548
00:32:02,120 --> 00:32:04,368
I can't help it.
I'm so hungry.

549
00:32:04,369 --> 00:32:05,497
I got to have a wildebeest.

550
00:32:05,623 --> 00:32:06,998
Stay put.

551
00:32:07,792 --> 00:32:09,539
Can't I just pick off
one of the little sick ones?

552
00:32:09,540 --> 00:32:13,338
No. We wait for the signal from Scar.

553
00:32:15,341 --> 00:32:18,969
There he is. Let's go.

554
00:32:19,428 --> 00:32:22,347
"Little roar." Puh!

555
00:32:24,684 --> 00:32:25,809
Rarr!

556
00:32:27,812 --> 00:32:29,020
Rrrarr!

557
00:32:32,984 --> 00:32:35,193
Rarr!

558
00:33:23,701 --> 00:33:25,660
Oh, look, sire, the herd is on the move.

559
00:33:25,745 --> 00:33:28,079
-Odd.
-Mufasa, quick.

560
00:33:28,164 --> 00:33:30,081
Stampede in the gorge.

561
00:33:30,166 --> 00:33:32,629
-Simba's down there!
-Simba?

562
00:33:54,899 --> 00:33:56,651
Zazu, help me!

563
00:33:56,652 --> 00:33:58,800
Your father is on the way! Hold on!

564
00:33:58,801 --> 00:33:59,736
Hurry!

565
00:34:03,199 --> 00:34:05,867
There! There on that tree!

566
00:34:05,952 --> 00:34:07,285
Hold on, Simba!

567
00:34:08,704 --> 00:34:10,205
Dad!

568
00:34:14,252 --> 00:34:16,294
ZAZU: Oh, Scar, this is awful!

569
00:34:16,379 --> 00:34:18,546
What'll we do? What'll we do?

570
00:34:18,631 --> 00:34:21,299
I'll go back for help,
that's what I'll do.

571
00:34:57,253 --> 00:34:58,336
Dad!

572
00:35:21,193 --> 00:35:22,861
MUFASA: Scar!

573
00:35:23,529 --> 00:35:26,531
-SCAR: Brother.
-Brother, help me!

574
00:35:34,540 --> 00:35:38,043
Long live the king.

575
00:35:43,049 --> 00:35:46,217
No!

576
00:35:59,065 --> 00:36:00,398
Dad!

577
00:36:12,745 --> 00:36:52,784
Dad?

578
00:36:53,661 --> 00:36:56,496
Dad, come on.

579
00:36:56,622 --> 00:36:59,457
You got to get up.

580
00:36:59,583 --> 00:37:01,543
Dad?

581
00:37:01,627 --> 00:37:03,586
We got to go home.

582
00:37:14,765 --> 00:37:16,266
Help!

583
00:37:18,811 --> 00:37:21,271
Somebody!

584
00:37:21,689 --> 00:37:23,148
Anybody.

585
00:37:24,859 --> 00:37:26,025
Help.

586
00:37:57,057 --> 00:38:00,727
Simba. What have you done?

587
00:38:02,354 --> 00:38:04,981
There were wildebeests,
and he tried to save me.

588
00:38:05,483 --> 00:38:08,234
It was an accident.
I didn't mean for it to happen.

589
00:38:08,360 --> 00:38:12,530
Of course.
Of course you didn't.

590
00:38:13,199 --> 00:38:18,077
No one ever means for
these things to happen.

591
00:38:18,204 --> 00:38:20,246
But the king is dead.

592
00:38:21,874 --> 00:38:24,876
And if it weren't for you,
he'd still be alive.

593
00:38:29,757 --> 00:38:32,217
Oh, what will your mother think?

594
00:38:33,429 --> 00:38:34,761
What am I going to do?

595
00:38:34,787 --> 00:38:36,221
Run away, Simba.

596
00:38:37,556 --> 00:38:42,602
Run. Run away and never return.

597
00:38:49,360 --> 00:38:50,735
Kill him.

598
00:39:28,148 --> 00:39:29,899
Whoa!

599
00:39:35,614 --> 00:39:37,740
Yow!

600
00:39:38,784 --> 00:39:40,410
Aah! Ohh! Yeow!

601
00:39:43,789 --> 00:39:45,790
Hey, there he goes.
There he goes.

602
00:39:46,458 --> 00:39:47,500
So go get him.

603
00:39:47,626 --> 00:39:49,419
There ain't no way
I'm going in there.

604
00:39:49,503 --> 00:39:51,453
What, you want me to come out
looking like you,

605
00:39:51,454 --> 00:39:53,423
cactus butt?

606
00:39:54,466 --> 00:39:55,800
But we got to finish the job.

607
00:39:55,926 --> 00:39:58,928
Well, he's as good as
dead out there anyway.

608
00:39:59,013 --> 00:40:01,806
And if he comes back, we'll kill him.

609
00:40:01,807 --> 00:40:03,780
Yeah! You hear that?

610
00:40:03,781 --> 00:40:07,478
If you ever come back, we'll kill you!

611
00:40:15,946 --> 00:40:20,043
Mufasa's death is a terrible tragedy.

612
00:40:20,044 --> 00:40:24,254
But to lose Simba,
who had barely begun to live...

613
00:40:25,456 --> 00:40:30,251
For me, it is a deep, personal loss.

614
00:40:30,336 --> 00:40:34,297
So it is with a heavy heart
that I assume the throne.

615
00:40:34,381 --> 00:40:38,635
Yet out of the ashes of this tragedy
we shall rise

616
00:40:38,719 --> 00:40:41,679
to greet the dawning of a new era

617
00:40:41,805 --> 00:40:45,558
in which lion and hyena come together

618
00:40:45,684 --> 00:40:49,979
in a great and glorious future.

619
00:41:32,564 --> 00:41:34,565
Yaaaah!

620
00:41:37,236 --> 00:41:39,404
Get out! Get out!
Get out of here!

621
00:41:39,530 --> 00:41:41,864
I love this! Bowling for buzzards.

622
00:41:42,074 --> 00:41:45,535
Hee hee hee!
Gets 'em every time.

623
00:41:45,744 --> 00:41:49,622
Uh-oh.
Hey, Timon, you better come look.

624
00:41:49,748 --> 00:41:51,749
I think it's still alive.

625
00:41:51,917 --> 00:41:53,126
Eeeuw.

626
00:41:53,419 --> 00:41:56,587
All righty, what have we got here?

627
00:42:02,553 --> 00:42:05,805
Jeez, it's a lion! Run, Pumbaa, move it!

628
00:42:05,931 --> 00:42:09,225
Hey, Timon, it's just a little lion.

629
00:42:09,309 --> 00:42:10,601
Look at him.

630
00:42:10,602 --> 00:42:13,938
He's so cute and all alone.

631
00:42:14,273 --> 00:42:16,441
-Can we keep him?
-Pumbaa, are you nuts?

632
00:42:16,525 --> 00:42:18,211
You're talking about a lion.

633
00:42:18,212 --> 00:42:19,777
Lions eat guys like us.

634
00:42:19,862 --> 00:42:22,280
-But he's so little.
-He's going to get bigger.

635
00:42:22,448 --> 00:42:23,494
Maybe he'll be on our side.

636
00:42:24,616 --> 00:42:27,702
That's the stupidest thing
I ever heard. Maybe he'll...

637
00:42:27,786 --> 00:42:29,448
Hey, I've got it.

638
00:42:29,449 --> 00:42:31,038
What if he's on our side?

639
00:42:31,123 --> 00:42:34,459
You know, having a lion around
might not be such a bad idea.

640
00:42:34,543 --> 00:42:35,626
So we're keeping him?

641
00:42:35,711 --> 00:42:37,962
Of course.
Who's the brains of this outfit?

642
00:42:38,046 --> 00:42:39,630
-Uh...
-My point exactly.

643
00:42:39,798 --> 00:42:40,896
Jeez, I'm fried.

644
00:42:40,897 --> 00:42:43,050
Let's get out of here
and find some shade.

645
00:42:51,643 --> 00:42:53,811
-You okay, kid?
-I guess so.

646
00:42:53,979 --> 00:42:55,313
You nearly died.

647
00:42:55,314 --> 00:42:56,447
I saved you.

648
00:42:56,448 --> 00:42:58,904
Well, Pumbaa helped. A little.

649
00:42:59,364 --> 00:43:01,068
Thanks for your help.

650
00:43:02,237 --> 00:43:03,488
Hey, where you going?

651
00:43:03,655 --> 00:43:05,823
Nowhere.

652
00:43:05,908 --> 00:43:07,241
Gee, he looks blue.

653
00:43:07,326 --> 00:43:09,151
I'd say brownish gold.

654
00:43:09,152 --> 00:43:11,421
No, no, no.
I mean he's depressed.

655
00:43:13,290 --> 00:43:14,769
-Kid, what's eating you?
-Nothing.

656
00:43:14,770 --> 00:43:17,502
He's at the top of the food chain.

657
00:43:19,922 --> 00:43:21,339
The food chain!

658
00:43:23,258 --> 00:43:24,342
Ahem.

659
00:43:25,511 --> 00:43:26,928
So, where you from?

660
00:43:27,012 --> 00:43:29,263
Who cares? I can't go back.

661
00:43:29,264 --> 00:43:30,947
Ah, you're an outcast.

662
00:43:30,948 --> 00:43:32,517
That's great. So are we.

663
00:43:32,643 --> 00:43:33,693
What'd you do, kid?

664
00:43:33,694 --> 00:43:35,102
Something terrible.

665
00:43:35,103 --> 00:43:36,561
But I don't want to talk about it.

666
00:43:36,562 --> 00:43:38,105
Good. We don't want to hear about it.

667
00:43:38,190 --> 00:43:40,358
Come on, Timon. Anything we can do?

668
00:43:40,484 --> 00:43:43,110
Not unless you can change the past.

669
00:43:43,195 --> 00:43:44,783
You know, kid, in times like this,

670
00:43:44,784 --> 00:43:46,447
my buddy Timon here says,

671
00:43:46,532 --> 00:43:49,359
"You got to put your
behind in your past."

672
00:43:49,360 --> 00:43:50,701
No, no, no.

673
00:43:50,828 --> 00:43:52,119
-I mean...
-Amateur.

674
00:43:52,204 --> 00:43:54,372
Lie down before you hurt yourself.

675
00:43:54,873 --> 00:43:57,625
It's,
"You got to put your past behind you."

676
00:43:57,709 --> 00:43:59,645
Look, kid, bad things happen,

677
00:43:59,646 --> 00:44:01,712
and you can't do anything
about it, right?

678
00:44:01,797 --> 00:44:02,797
-Right.
-Wrong!

679
00:44:02,881 --> 00:44:05,633
When the world turns its back on you,

680
00:44:05,634 --> 00:44:08,302
you turn your back on the world.

681
00:44:08,387 --> 00:44:10,304
Well, that's not what I was taught.

682
00:44:10,389 --> 00:44:12,557
Then maybe you need a new lesson.

683
00:44:12,724 --> 00:44:14,976
Repeat after me. Ahem.

684
00:44:15,060 --> 00:44:16,894
-Hakuna matata.
-What?

685
00:44:17,354 --> 00:44:19,897
Hakuna matata.

686
00:44:20,023 --> 00:44:21,232
It means "no worries".

687
00:44:21,733 --> 00:44:24,235
<i>♪ Hakuna matata. ♪</i>

688
00:44:24,361 --> 00:44:27,488
<i>♪ What a wonderful phrase ♪</i>

689
00:44:27,573 --> 00:44:29,907
<i>♪ Hakuna matata ♪</i>

690
00:44:30,033 --> 00:44:33,244
<i>♪ Ain't no passing craze ♪</i>

691
00:44:33,370 --> 00:44:35,891
<i>♪ It means no worries ♪</i>

692
00:44:35,892 --> 00:44:39,834
<i>♪ For the rest of your days ♪</i>

693
00:44:39,918 --> 00:44:44,922
<i>♪ It's our problem-free philosophy ♪</i>

694
00:44:45,048 --> 00:44:47,508
<i>♪ Hakuna matata ♪</i>

695
00:44:47,593 --> 00:44:49,343
Hakuna matata?

696
00:44:49,428 --> 00:44:50,752
Yeah. It's our motto.

697
00:44:50,753 --> 00:44:52,013
What's a motto?

698
00:44:52,097 --> 00:44:54,432
Nothin'. What's-a-motto with you?

699
00:44:55,559 --> 00:44:59,620
You know, kid, these two words
will solve all your problems.

700
00:44:59,621 --> 00:45:01,852
That's right.
Take Pumbaa, for example.

701
00:45:01,853 --> 00:45:02,773
Why...

702
00:45:02,900 --> 00:45:05,610
<i>♪ When he was
a young warthog ♪</i>

703
00:45:05,944 --> 00:45:09,530
<i>♪ When I was a young warthog ♪</i>

704
00:45:09,615 --> 00:45:11,449
-Very nice.
-Thanks.

705
00:45:11,809 --> 00:45:14,327
<i>♪ He found his aroma
lacked a certain appeal ♪</i>

706
00:45:14,328 --> 00:45:16,787
<i>♪ He could clear the savanna
after every meal ♪</i>

707
00:45:16,914 --> 00:45:18,956
<i>♪ I'm a sensitive soul ♪</i>

708
00:45:19,082 --> 00:45:21,542
<i>♪ Though I seem thick-skinned ♪</i>

709
00:45:22,794 --> 00:45:27,965
<i>♪ And it hurt that my friends
never stood downwind ♪</i>

710
00:45:28,050 --> 00:45:31,426
-And, oh, the shame
-He was ashamed

711
00:45:31,427 --> 00:45:34,138
-Thought of changing my name
-Oh, what's in a name?

712
00:45:34,264 --> 00:45:35,806
And I got downhearted

713
00:45:35,891 --> 00:45:37,808
-How did you feel?
-Every time that I...

714
00:45:37,935 --> 00:45:39,742
Hey, not in front of the kids.

715
00:45:39,743 --> 00:45:40,645
Oh, sorry.

716
00:45:41,405 --> 00:45:43,648
Hakuna matata

717
00:45:43,774 --> 00:45:46,984
What a wonderful phrase

718
00:45:47,110 --> 00:45:48,903
Hakuna matata

719
00:45:48,987 --> 00:45:52,156
Ain't no passing craze

720
00:45:52,282 --> 00:45:54,492
It means no worries

721
00:45:54,576 --> 00:45:56,698
For the rest of your days

722
00:45:56,699 --> 00:45:58,162
Yeah, sing it, kid.

723
00:45:58,288 --> 00:46:03,918
<i>♪ It's our problem-free
Philosophy ♪</i>

724
00:46:04,002 --> 00:46:07,296
<i>♪ Hakuna matata ♪</i>

725
00:46:08,006 --> 00:46:10,007
Welcome to our humble home.

726
00:46:10,008 --> 00:46:11,313
You live here?

727
00:46:11,314 --> 00:46:12,776
We live wherever we want.

728
00:46:12,777 --> 00:46:15,137
Yep. Home is where your rump rests.

729
00:46:15,263 --> 00:46:16,792
It's beautiful.

730
00:46:18,000 --> 00:46:19,229
I'm starved.

731
00:46:19,230 --> 00:46:21,519
I'm so hungry I could eat a whole zebra.

732
00:46:22,187 --> 00:46:24,355
Ah. We're fresh out of zebra.

733
00:46:24,439 --> 00:46:26,107
-Any antelope?
-Nuh-uh.

734
00:46:26,191 --> 00:46:27,775
-Hippo?
-Nope.

735
00:46:27,859 --> 00:46:31,028
Listen, kid, if you live with us,
you have to eat like us.

736
00:46:31,113 --> 00:46:33,656
Hey, this looks like a good spot
to rustle up some grub.

737
00:46:34,866 --> 00:46:36,200
Eugh, what's that?

738
00:46:36,326 --> 00:46:38,119
A grub. What's it look like?

739
00:46:38,203 --> 00:46:40,162
Eugh! Gross.

740
00:46:40,372 --> 00:46:42,707
Mmm. Tastes like chicken.

741
00:46:43,875 --> 00:46:46,544
Slimy yet satisfying.

742
00:46:46,628 --> 00:46:49,296
These are rare delicacies. Mmm.

743
00:46:50,132 --> 00:46:53,217
Piquant, with a very pleasant crunch.

744
00:46:53,385 --> 00:46:54,969
You'll learn to love them.

745
00:46:55,053 --> 00:46:57,388
I'm telling you, kid, this is the great life,

746
00:46:57,514 --> 00:46:59,807
no rules, no responsibilities.

747
00:46:59,891 --> 00:47:02,560
Ooh, the little cream-filled kind.

748
00:47:02,644 --> 00:47:05,396
And best of all, no worries.

749
00:47:05,397 --> 00:47:07,314
Well, kid?

750
00:47:07,399 --> 00:47:10,234
Oh, well. Hakuna matata.

751
00:47:14,906 --> 00:47:17,658
Slimy, yet satisfying.

752
00:47:17,743 --> 00:47:19,243
That's it.

753
00:47:31,673 --> 00:47:35,843
<i>♪ Hakuna matata ♪</i>

754
00:47:35,927 --> 00:47:38,596
<i>♪ -Hakuna...
-It means no worries ♪</i>

755
00:47:38,680 --> 00:47:41,766
<i>♪ For the rest of your days ♪</i>

756
00:47:42,267 --> 00:47:47,354
<i>♪ It's our problem-free
Philosophy ♪</i>

757
00:47:47,439 --> 00:48:03,287
<i>♪ Hakuna matata ♪</i>

758
00:48:03,455 --> 00:48:04,872
Brrrrrr!

759
00:48:05,082 --> 00:48:12,963
Hakuna matata

760
00:48:13,048 --> 00:48:14,632
Yeah

761
00:48:14,716 --> 00:48:16,300
Ta-ta!

762
00:48:16,468 --> 00:48:18,219
Ha ha ha!

763
00:48:24,101 --> 00:48:27,394
<i>♪ Nobody knows ♪</i>

764
00:48:27,479 --> 00:48:30,898
<i>♪ The trouble I've seen ♪</i>

765
00:48:30,982 --> 00:48:34,735
<i>♪ Nobody knows ♪</i>

766
00:48:34,820 --> 00:48:36,737
<i>♪ My sorrow ♪</i>

767
00:48:36,822 --> 00:48:38,989
Oh, Zazu, do lighten up.

768
00:48:39,407 --> 00:48:42,326
Sing something with a little bounce in it.

769
00:48:43,578 --> 00:48:46,163
<i>♪ lt's a small world after all ♪</i>

770
00:48:46,248 --> 00:48:49,458
No, no!
Anything but that!

771
00:48:50,961 --> 00:48:53,582
<i>♪ l've got
a lovely bunch of coconuts ♪</i>

772
00:48:53,583 --> 00:48:54,529
<i>♪ Deedle dee dee ♪</i>

773
00:48:54,530 --> 00:48:58,175
<i>♪ <i>♪ There they are a-standing in a row ♪</i> ♪</i>

774
00:48:58,343 --> 00:49:01,428
<i>♪ Big ones, small ones,
some as big as your head ♪</i>

775
00:49:01,596 --> 00:49:04,515
I would never have had
to do this with Mufasa.

776
00:49:04,599 --> 00:49:06,600
What? What did you say?

777
00:49:06,685 --> 00:49:08,936
-Nothing.
-You know the law.

778
00:49:09,020 --> 00:49:12,266
Never, ever mention that name
in my presence.

779
00:49:12,267 --> 00:49:13,440
I am the king!

780
00:49:14,025 --> 00:49:16,026
Yes, sire, you are the king.

781
00:49:16,111 --> 00:49:19,113
I... I only mentioned it
to illustrate the differences

782
00:49:19,197 --> 00:49:21,847
in your royal managerial approaches.

783
00:49:21,848 --> 00:49:22,848
BANZAI: Hey, boss.

784
00:49:22,849 --> 00:49:24,952
Oh, what is it this time?

785
00:49:25,036 --> 00:49:26,377
We got a bone to pick with you.

786
00:49:26,378 --> 00:49:27,499
I'll handle this.

787
00:49:27,500 --> 00:49:29,957
Scar, there's no food, no water.

788
00:49:29,958 --> 00:49:31,850
Yeah. It's dinner time

789
00:49:31,851 --> 00:49:33,878
and we ain't got no stinking entrées.

790
00:49:34,045 --> 00:49:38,094
It's the lionesses' job to do the hunting.

791
00:49:38,095 --> 00:49:39,375
Yeah, but they won't go hunt.

792
00:49:39,376 --> 00:49:40,531
Oh...

793
00:49:40,532 --> 00:49:41,575
Eat Zazu.

794
00:49:41,576 --> 00:49:43,840
Oh, you wouldn't want me.

795
00:49:43,841 --> 00:49:46,473
I'd be so tough and gamey and...

796
00:49:46,558 --> 00:49:49,977
Oh, Zazu, don't be ridiculous.
All you need is a little garlic.

797
00:49:50,061 --> 00:49:52,146
I thought things
were bad under Mufasa.

798
00:49:52,230 --> 00:49:54,732
-What did you say?
-I said Muf...

799
00:49:54,858 --> 00:49:56,400
I said qué pasa?

800
00:49:56,568 --> 00:49:58,903
Good. Now get out.

801
00:50:01,239 --> 00:50:02,489
But we're still hungry.

802
00:50:02,574 --> 00:50:04,575
Out!

803
00:50:11,333 --> 00:50:14,501
-Whoa! Nice one, Simba.
-Thanks.

804
00:50:14,586 --> 00:50:17,504
-Man, I'm stuffed.
-Me, too.

805
00:50:17,589 --> 00:50:19,840
I ate like a pig.

806
00:50:19,925 --> 00:50:22,009
Pumbaa, you are a pig.

807
00:50:22,093 --> 00:50:24,094
Oh. Right.

808
00:50:35,106 --> 00:50:37,858
-Timon?
-Yeah?

809
00:50:37,943 --> 00:50:42,029
Ever wonder what those
sparkling dots are up there?

810
00:50:42,113 --> 00:50:45,366
Pumbaa, I don't wonder, I know.

811
00:50:45,367 --> 00:50:48,202
Oh? What are they?

812
00:50:48,286 --> 00:50:50,037
They're fireflies.

813
00:50:50,121 --> 00:50:54,541
Fireflies that got stuck
up in that big bluish-black thing.

814
00:50:54,626 --> 00:50:56,627
Oh, gee.

815
00:50:57,087 --> 00:50:59,964
I always thought they were balls of gas

816
00:50:59,965 --> 00:51:03,467
burning billions of miles away.

817
00:51:04,135 --> 00:51:07,221
Pumbaa, with you, everything's gas.

818
00:51:07,305 --> 00:51:09,306
Simba, what do you think?

819
00:51:09,724 --> 00:51:11,392
Well, I don't know.

820
00:51:11,476 --> 00:51:13,477
Oh, come on.
Give, give, give, give.

821
00:51:13,603 --> 00:51:15,740
Come on. We told you ours.

822
00:51:15,741 --> 00:51:18,649
- Please?
- Well...

823
00:51:18,650 --> 00:51:20,818
Somebody once told me

824
00:51:21,069 --> 00:51:23,757
that the great kings of the past
are up there

825
00:51:23,758 --> 00:51:25,406
watching over us.

826
00:51:25,490 --> 00:51:26,573
Really?

827
00:51:26,658 --> 00:51:30,035
You mean a bunch of royal dead guys
are watching us?

828
00:51:30,370 --> 00:51:31,537
Pfff!

829
00:51:35,375 --> 00:51:37,105
Who told you something like that?

830
00:51:37,106 --> 00:51:38,252
Yeah, yeah.

831
00:51:38,336 --> 00:51:43,007
-What mook made that up?
-Yeah. Pretty dumb, huh?

832
00:51:43,091 --> 00:51:46,176
-Aw, you're killing me.
-Yeah.

833
00:51:56,446 --> 00:51:58,731
Was it something I said?

834
00:52:25,508 --> 00:52:26,592
Hmm.

835
00:52:49,157 --> 00:52:50,240
Hmm.

836
00:52:50,950 --> 00:52:52,743
Simba?

837
00:52:52,827 --> 00:52:55,537
He's... He's alive?
He's alive!

838
00:53:10,887 --> 00:53:12,471
It is time.

839
00:53:17,227 --> 00:53:19,186
<i>♪ A-wimoweh, a-wimoweh ♪</i>

840
00:53:19,270 --> 00:53:21,188
<i>♪ A-wimoweh, a-wimoweh ♪</i>

841
00:53:21,272 --> 00:53:25,401
<i>♪ In the jungle, the mighty jungle ♪</i>

842
00:53:25,485 --> 00:53:29,446
<i>♪ The lion sleeps tonight ♪</i>

843
00:53:29,531 --> 00:53:33,450
<i>♪ In the jungle, the mighty jungle ♪</i>

844
00:53:33,535 --> 00:53:35,369
<i>♪ The lion sleeps to... ♪</i>

845
00:53:35,453 --> 00:53:37,621
I can't hear you, buddy.
Back me up.

846
00:53:37,914 --> 00:53:40,124
<i>♪ A-wiiiiii ♪</i>

847
00:53:40,208 --> 00:53:41,291
<i>♪ Iiiiii-iiiiii-iiii ♪</i>

848
00:53:41,376 --> 00:53:45,003
<i>♪ A-Pumbaa-bum-baa-weh ♪</i>

849
00:53:45,255 --> 00:53:47,214
Pumbaa? Pumbaa?

850
00:53:51,177 --> 00:53:52,219
Hmm?

851
00:54:03,398 --> 00:54:04,440
Timon?

852
00:54:19,038 --> 00:54:20,164
Aaggghh!

853
00:54:27,714 --> 00:54:29,882
Pumbaa?

854
00:54:33,052 --> 00:54:34,845
Pumbaa! Pumbaa!

855
00:54:36,055 --> 00:54:38,348
Pumbaa, Pumbaa!
Hey, what's going on?

856
00:54:38,433 --> 00:54:40,893
-She's going to eat me!
-Huh?

857
00:54:41,895 --> 00:54:46,565
Whoa! Jeez, why do I always
have to save your...

858
00:54:52,405 --> 00:54:54,136
Don't worry, buddy. I'm here for you.

859
00:54:54,137 --> 00:54:56,408
Everything's going to be okay.

860
00:54:56,534 --> 00:54:59,703
Get her! Bite her head!

861
00:54:59,787 --> 00:55:02,623
Go for the jugular! The jugular!

862
00:55:02,749 --> 00:55:04,917
See, I told you he'd come in handy.

863
00:55:09,383 --> 00:55:10,797
Nala?

864
00:55:14,552 --> 00:55:16,261
Is it really you?

865
00:55:16,471 --> 00:55:17,972
Who are you?

866
00:55:17,973 --> 00:55:20,174
It's me. Simba.

867
00:55:21,434 --> 00:55:22,197
Simba?

868
00:55:25,146 --> 00:55:27,295
Whoa!

869
00:55:27,296 --> 00:55:28,398
How did you...

870
00:55:29,776 --> 00:55:31,568
-Wow!
-Where did you come from?

871
00:55:31,653 --> 00:55:33,654
This is gr... It's great to see you!

872
00:55:33,780 --> 00:55:35,884
Hey, what's goin' on here?

873
00:55:35,885 --> 00:55:36,698
What are you doing here?

874
00:55:36,783 --> 00:55:38,909
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?

875
00:55:38,993 --> 00:55:42,171
Hey! What's goin' on here?

876
00:55:42,172 --> 00:55:45,374
Timon, this is Nala.
She's my best friend.

877
00:55:45,458 --> 00:55:46,983
- Friend?
- Yeah.

878
00:55:46,984 --> 00:55:49,461
Hey, Pumbaa, come over here.

879
00:55:49,546 --> 00:55:50,587
Huh?

880
00:55:50,672 --> 00:55:53,131
Nala, this is Pumbaa. Pumbaa, Nala.

881
00:55:53,132 --> 00:55:55,759
-Pleased to make your acquaintance.
-The pleasure is all mine.

882
00:55:55,843 --> 00:55:57,481
How do you... Whoa, whoa!

883
00:55:57,482 --> 00:55:59,813
Time out!
Let me get this straight.

884
00:56:00,106 --> 00:56:02,015
You know her, she knows you.

885
00:56:02,100 --> 00:56:03,936
But she wants to eat him,

886
00:56:03,937 --> 00:56:06,687
and everybody's okay with this?

887
00:56:06,813 --> 00:56:09,562
-Did I miss something?
-Relax, Timon.

888
00:56:09,563 --> 00:56:12,484
Wait till everyone finds out
you've been here all this time.

889
00:56:13,111 --> 00:56:16,029
And your mother, what will she think?

890
00:56:16,114 --> 00:56:19,491
She doesn't have to know.
Nobody has to know.

891
00:56:19,576 --> 00:56:21,827
Of course they do.
Everyone thinks you're dead.

892
00:56:21,995 --> 00:56:23,078
They do?

893
00:56:23,162 --> 00:56:26,373
Yeah. Scar told us about the stampede.

894
00:56:26,541 --> 00:56:29,735
He did? What else did he tell you?

895
00:56:29,736 --> 00:56:31,853
What else matters? You're alive.

896
00:56:31,854 --> 00:56:35,349
And that means, you're the king.

897
00:56:35,350 --> 00:56:36,838
King?

898
00:56:37,485 --> 00:56:40,804
Lady, have you got
your lions crossed!

899
00:56:40,888 --> 00:56:42,055
King?

900
00:56:42,140 --> 00:56:46,226
Your Majesty, I gravel at your feet.
Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!

901
00:56:46,352 --> 00:56:47,291
Stop it.

902
00:56:47,292 --> 00:56:49,229
It's not gravel, it's grovel.

903
00:56:49,314 --> 00:56:52,277
And don't! He's not the king.

904
00:56:52,278 --> 00:56:52,883
Are you?

905
00:56:52,884 --> 00:56:54,264
-No.
-Simba!

906
00:56:54,265 --> 00:56:57,286
No, I'm not the king.
Maybe I was gonna be,

907
00:56:57,287 --> 00:56:59,288
but that was a long time ago.

908
00:56:59,289 --> 00:57:00,671
Let me get this straight.

909
00:57:00,672 --> 00:57:03,285
You're the king?
And you never told us?

910
00:57:03,369 --> 00:57:06,121
-Look, I'm still the same guy.
-But with power.

911
00:57:06,205 --> 00:57:09,082
Could you guys excuse us
for a few minutes?

912
00:57:09,334 --> 00:57:11,126
Hey, whatever she has to say,

913
00:57:11,127 --> 00:57:13,295
she can say in front of us, right, Simba?

914
00:57:13,921 --> 00:57:15,047
Mm...

915
00:57:15,506 --> 00:57:16,800
Maybe you'd better go.

916
00:57:18,217 --> 00:57:21,345
It starts.
You think you know a guy.

917
00:57:24,724 --> 00:57:28,268
Timon and Pumbaa,
you learn to love 'em.

918
00:57:30,605 --> 00:57:32,022
What?

919
00:57:33,733 --> 00:57:34,816
What is it?

920
00:57:35,985 --> 00:57:38,278
It's like you're back from the dead.

921
00:57:38,821 --> 00:57:42,324
You don't know how much
this will mean to everyone.

922
00:57:42,700 --> 00:57:44,284
What it means to me.

923
00:57:44,369 --> 00:57:48,163
-Hey, it's okay.
-I've really missed you.

924
00:57:48,247 --> 00:57:50,749
I've missed you, too.

925
00:57:52,543 --> 00:57:56,363
I tell you, Pumbaa.
This stinks.

926
00:57:56,364 --> 00:57:57,964
Oh, sorry.

927
00:57:58,049 --> 00:58:00,217
Not you! Them!

928
00:58:00,760 --> 00:58:03,722
Him, her, alone.

929
00:58:04,024 --> 00:58:05,430
What's wrong with that?

930
00:58:05,515 --> 00:58:07,214
<i>♪ I can see what's happening ♪</i>

931
00:58:07,215 --> 00:58:08,016
What?

932
00:58:08,017 --> 00:58:09,937
<i>♪ And they don't have a clue ♪</i>

933
00:58:09,938 --> 00:58:10,686
Who?

934
00:58:10,687 --> 00:58:14,189
<i>♪ They'll fall in love
and here's the bottom line ♪</i>

935
00:58:14,273 --> 00:58:16,414
<i>♪ Our trio's down to two ♪</i>

936
00:58:16,415 --> 00:58:17,192
Oh.

937
00:58:17,360 --> 00:58:20,487
<i>♪ The sweet caress of twilight ♪</i>

938
00:58:20,488 --> 00:58:23,532
<i>♪ There's magic everywhere ♪</i>

939
00:58:23,533 --> 00:58:29,121
<i>♪ And with all this
romantic atmosphere ♪</i>

940
00:58:29,122 --> 00:58:33,375
<i>♪ Disaster's in the air ♪</i>

941
00:58:38,214 --> 00:58:44,886
<i>♪ Can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

942
00:58:44,887 --> 00:58:50,392
<i>♪ The peace the evening brings ♪</i>

943
00:58:50,393 --> 00:58:53,562
<i>♪ The world for once ♪</i>

944
00:58:53,563 --> 00:58:56,732
<i>♪ In perfect harmony ♪</i>

945
00:58:56,816 --> 00:59:02,070
<i>♪ With all its living things ♪</i>

946
00:59:03,197 --> 00:59:06,347
<i>♪ So many things to tell her ♪</i>

947
00:59:06,348 --> 00:59:09,453
<i>♪ But how to make her see ♪</i>

948
00:59:09,454 --> 00:59:12,122
<i>♪ The truth about my past? ♪</i>

949
00:59:12,123 --> 00:59:15,751
<i>♪ Impossible, she'd turn away from me ♪</i>

950
00:59:15,835 --> 00:59:19,171
<i>♪ He's holding back, he's hiding ♪</i>

951
00:59:19,172 --> 00:59:22,424
<i>♪ But what, I can't decide ♪</i>

952
00:59:22,425 --> 00:59:25,802
<i>♪ Why won't he be
the king I know he is? ♪</i>

953
00:59:25,803 --> 00:59:30,557
<i>♪ The king I see inside? ♪</i>

954
00:59:30,558 --> 00:59:36,354
<i>♪ Can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

955
00:59:37,398 --> 00:59:41,818
<i>♪ The peace the evening brings ♪</i>

956
00:59:42,945 --> 00:59:45,655
<i>♪ The world for once ♪</i>

957
00:59:45,740 --> 00:59:48,950
<i>♪ In perfect harmony ♪</i>

958
00:59:49,035 --> 00:59:53,997
<i>♪ With all its living things ♪</i>

959
00:59:56,000 --> 01:00:01,546
<i>♪ Can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

960
01:00:02,673 --> 01:00:07,511
<i>♪ You needn't look too far ♪</i>

961
01:00:08,888 --> 01:00:11,306
<i>♪ Stealing through ♪</i>

962
01:00:11,307 --> 01:00:14,851
<i>♪ The night's uncertainties ♪</i>

963
01:00:14,852 --> 01:00:19,731
<i>♪ Love is where they are ♪</i>

964
01:00:20,900 --> 01:00:27,295
<i>♪ And if he falls in love tonight ♪</i>

965
01:00:28,115 --> 01:00:34,126
<i>♪ It can be assumed ♪</i>

966
01:00:34,127 --> 01:00:36,706
<i>♪ His carefree days ♪</i>

967
01:00:36,707 --> 01:00:40,168
<i>♪ With us are history ♪</i>

968
01:00:40,169 --> 01:00:44,256
<i>♪ In short, our pal ♪</i>

969
01:00:44,257 --> 01:00:51,067
<i>♪ Is doomed ♪</i>

970
01:00:58,771 --> 01:01:00,438
Isn't this a great place?

971
01:01:00,523 --> 01:01:02,524
It is beautiful.

972
01:01:02,859 --> 01:01:05,485
But I don't understand something.

973
01:01:05,570 --> 01:01:08,280
You've been alive all this time.

974
01:01:08,281 --> 01:01:10,365
Why didn't you
come back to Pride Rock?

975
01:01:10,449 --> 01:01:13,919
Well, I just needed
to get out on my own,

976
01:01:13,920 --> 01:01:15,287
live my own life.

977
01:01:15,371 --> 01:01:17,065
And I did, and it's great.

978
01:01:17,470 --> 01:01:19,177
We've really needed you at home.

979
01:01:19,876 --> 01:01:21,129
No one needs me.

980
01:01:21,130 --> 01:01:23,450
Yes, we do. You're the king.

981
01:01:23,451 --> 01:01:25,825
Nala, we've been through this.
I'm not the king.

982
01:01:25,826 --> 01:01:27,549
Scar is.

983
01:01:27,550 --> 01:01:30,795
Simba, he let the hyenas
take over the Pride Lands.

984
01:01:30,796 --> 01:01:32,971
-What?
-Everything's destroyed.

985
01:01:32,972 --> 01:01:34,598
There's no food, no water.

986
01:01:34,682 --> 01:01:36,452
Simba, if you don't do something soon,

987
01:01:36,453 --> 01:01:37,475
everyone will starve.

988
01:01:37,476 --> 01:01:38,810
-I can't go back.
-Why?

989
01:01:38,811 --> 01:01:41,027
-You wouldn't understand.
-What?

990
01:01:41,028 --> 01:01:42,552
No, no, no. It doesn't matter.

991
01:01:42,553 --> 01:01:43,815
Hakuna matata.

992
01:01:43,816 --> 01:01:45,650
-What?
-Hakuna matata.

993
01:01:45,651 --> 01:01:47,471
It's something I learned out here.

994
01:01:47,472 --> 01:01:49,437
Sometimes bad things happen...

995
01:01:49,438 --> 01:01:50,032
Simba...

996
01:01:50,033 --> 01:01:53,707
...and there's nothing you can do
about it. So why worry?

997
01:01:53,708 --> 01:01:55,358
Because it's your responsibility.

998
01:01:56,693 --> 01:01:58,130
Well, what about you?
You left.

999
01:01:58,456 --> 01:02:01,291
I left to find help, and I found you.

1000
01:02:01,500 --> 01:02:02,960
Don't you understand?

1001
01:02:02,961 --> 01:02:05,795
You're our only hope.

1002
01:02:05,880 --> 01:02:09,215
-Sorry.
-What's happened to you?

1003
01:02:09,216 --> 01:02:10,626
You're not the Simba I remember.

1004
01:02:10,627 --> 01:02:12,844
You're right. I'm not.

1005
01:02:12,845 --> 01:02:16,195
-Now are you satisfied?
-No. Just disappointed.

1006
01:02:16,315 --> 01:02:19,309
You know, you're starting
to sound like my father.

1007
01:02:19,393 --> 01:02:22,110
Good. At least one of us does.

1008
01:02:22,111 --> 01:02:25,857
You think you can just show up
and tell me how to live my life?

1009
01:02:25,858 --> 01:02:27,385
You don't even know
what I've been through.

1010
01:02:27,386 --> 01:02:29,261
I would if you'd just tell me.

1011
01:02:29,262 --> 01:02:31,196
-Forget it!
-Fine!

1012
01:02:34,769 --> 01:02:37,869
She's wrong. I can't go back.

1013
01:02:38,329 --> 01:02:42,040
What would it prove, anyway?
It won't change anything.

1014
01:02:42,291 --> 01:02:44,125
You can't change the past.

1015
01:02:47,296 --> 01:02:49,900
You said you'd always be there for me!

1016
01:02:50,697 --> 01:02:52,593
But you're not.

1017
01:02:54,545 --> 01:02:57,138
And it's because of me.

1018
01:02:57,682 --> 01:02:59,543
It's my fault.

1019
01:03:00,270 --> 01:03:03,021
It's my fault.

1020
01:03:06,399 --> 01:03:08,400
<i>♪ Asante sana,
squash banana ♪</i>

1021
01:03:08,484 --> 01:03:09,818
<i>♪ We we nugu, imi mi apana ♪</i>

1022
01:03:09,902 --> 01:03:11,695
<i>♪ Asante sana, squash banana ♪</i>

1023
01:03:11,779 --> 01:03:13,488
<i>♪ We we nugu, imi mi apana ♪</i>

1024
01:03:13,572 --> 01:03:15,490
<i>♪ Asante sana, squash banana ♪</i>

1025
01:03:15,574 --> 01:03:17,659
<i>♪ We we nugu, imi mi apana ♪</i>

1026
01:03:41,767 --> 01:03:45,687
<i>♪ Asante sana, squash banana
We we nugu, imi mi apana ♪</i>

1027
01:03:47,356 --> 01:03:48,982
Come on, will you cut it out?

1028
01:03:49,008 --> 01:03:51,985
Can't cut it out.
It'll grow right back!

1029
01:03:52,111 --> 01:03:53,882
Creepy little monkey.

1030
01:03:53,883 --> 01:03:55,155
Will you stop following me?

1031
01:03:55,584 --> 01:03:59,317
-Who are you?
-The question is, who are you?

1032
01:04:01,766 --> 01:04:03,922
I thought I knew.

1033
01:04:03,923 --> 01:04:05,022
Now I'm not so sure.

1034
01:04:05,023 --> 01:04:09,210
Well, I know who you are.
Shh. Come here. It's a secret.

1035
01:04:09,295 --> 01:04:12,714
<i>♪ Asante sana, squash banana ♪</i>

1036
01:04:12,798 --> 01:04:15,399
Grrr! Enough!
What is that supposed to mean?

1037
01:04:15,400 --> 01:04:17,403
It means you are a baboon,

1038
01:04:17,404 --> 01:04:18,636
and I'm not.

1039
01:04:20,306 --> 01:04:22,640
I think you're a little confused.

1040
01:04:22,641 --> 01:04:25,518
Wrong! I'm not the one who's confused.

1041
01:04:25,644 --> 01:04:27,354
You don't even know who you are.

1042
01:04:27,355 --> 01:04:29,064
Oh, and I suppose you know.

1043
01:04:29,148 --> 01:04:32,150
Sure do. You're Mufasa's boy.

1044
01:04:33,652 --> 01:04:36,362
-Bye.
-Hey, wait!

1045
01:04:45,331 --> 01:04:46,372
You knew my father?

1046
01:04:46,457 --> 01:04:49,667
Correction, I know your father.

1047
01:04:51,921 --> 01:04:53,838
I hate to tell you this,

1048
01:04:53,839 --> 01:04:56,925
but he died a long time ago.

1049
01:04:57,009 --> 01:04:59,135
Nope. Wrong again!

1050
01:04:59,220 --> 01:05:00,512
Ha ha ha!

1051
01:05:00,679 --> 01:05:03,431
He's alive, and I'll show him to you.

1052
01:05:03,516 --> 01:05:06,097
You follow old Rafiki.
He knows the way.

1053
01:05:06,098 --> 01:05:06,718
Come on!

1054
01:05:16,445 --> 01:05:18,613
Don't dawdle. Hurry up!

1055
01:05:18,697 --> 01:05:20,428
Hey, whoa, wait, wait.

1056
01:05:20,429 --> 01:05:22,158
Come on. Come on!

1057
01:05:23,869 --> 01:05:26,037
Would you slow down?

1058
01:05:37,216 --> 01:05:39,384
Stop!

1059
01:05:44,223 --> 01:05:45,723
Look down there.

1060
01:06:10,816 --> 01:06:13,877
That's not my father.
That's just my reflection.

1061
01:06:13,961 --> 01:06:15,628
No.

1062
01:06:16,755 --> 01:06:19,591
Look harder.

1063
01:06:25,806 --> 01:06:27,140
You see?

1064
01:06:28,434 --> 01:06:30,935
He lives in you.

1065
01:06:35,107 --> 01:06:37,775
MUFASA: Simba.

1066
01:06:37,860 --> 01:06:39,485
Father?

1067
01:06:47,411 --> 01:06:50,163
Simba, you have forgotten me.

1068
01:06:50,289 --> 01:06:52,373
No. How could I?

1069
01:06:52,458 --> 01:06:57,212
You have forgotten who you are,
and so have forgotten me.

1070
01:06:57,296 --> 01:06:59,964
Look inside yourself, Simba.

1071
01:06:59,965 --> 01:07:03,801
You are more than
what you have become.

1072
01:07:03,802 --> 01:07:07,138
You must take your place
in the circle of life.

1073
01:07:07,223 --> 01:07:09,304
How can I go back?

1074
01:07:09,305 --> 01:07:11,142
I'm not who I used to be.

1075
01:07:11,310 --> 01:07:15,146
Remember who you are.

1076
01:07:15,231 --> 01:07:19,150
You are my son
and the one true king.

1077
01:07:21,028 --> 01:07:24,656
Remember who you are.

1078
01:07:24,740 --> 01:07:27,575
No! Please, don't leave me!

1079
01:07:27,660 --> 01:07:28,710
MUFASA: Remember.

1080
01:07:28,711 --> 01:07:30,822
-Father!
-Remember!

1081
01:07:30,823 --> 01:07:32,622
Don't leave me.

1082
01:07:32,623 --> 01:07:34,540
Remember.

1083
01:07:43,133 --> 01:07:45,076
What was that? Ha ha!

1084
01:07:45,261 --> 01:07:46,970
The weather.

1085
01:07:47,054 --> 01:07:49,745
Very peculiar, don't you think?

1086
01:07:49,746 --> 01:07:50,723
Yeah.

1087
01:07:51,308 --> 01:07:52,809
Looks like the winds are changing.

1088
01:07:52,893 --> 01:07:55,436
Ahh, change is good.

1089
01:07:55,854 --> 01:07:57,689
Yeah, but it's not easy.

1090
01:07:57,773 --> 01:07:59,775
I know what I have to do, but...

1091
01:07:59,776 --> 01:08:02,577
going back means
I'll have to face my past.

1092
01:08:03,862 --> 01:08:05,947
I've been running from it
for so long.

1093
01:08:06,865 --> 01:08:09,200
Ow! Jeez!
What was that for?

1094
01:08:09,285 --> 01:08:12,161
It doesn't matter.
It's in the past.

1095
01:08:12,246 --> 01:08:14,247
Yeah, but it still hurts.

1096
01:08:14,331 --> 01:08:16,624
Oh, yes, the past can hurt.

1097
01:08:16,709 --> 01:08:20,295
But the way I see it
you can either run from it

1098
01:08:20,379 --> 01:08:23,214
or learn from it.

1099
01:08:23,299 --> 01:08:26,092
Ah! You see?
So what are you going to do?

1100
01:08:26,302 --> 01:08:28,761
First, I'm gonna take your stick.

1101
01:08:28,846 --> 01:08:31,097
No, no, no, no! Not the stick!

1102
01:08:31,181 --> 01:08:34,767
-Hey! Where are you going?
-I'm going back!

1103
01:08:34,852 --> 01:08:37,770
Good! Go on! Get out of here!

1104
01:08:40,399 --> 01:08:42,734
Whoo! Ha ha ha!

1105
01:08:42,818 --> 01:08:46,821
Whoooo! Whoooo!

1106
01:08:54,663 --> 01:08:55,830
Grubs! Grubs!

1107
01:09:01,378 --> 01:09:03,338
Hey. Hey, wake up.

1108
01:09:07,243 --> 01:09:10,762
It's okay! Whoa, whoa!
It's okay! It's me!

1109
01:09:11,847 --> 01:09:14,307
Don't ever do that again.

1110
01:09:14,600 --> 01:09:16,309
Carnivores! Oy!

1111
01:09:16,393 --> 01:09:19,020
-Have you guys seen Simba?
-I thought he was with you.

1112
01:09:19,104 --> 01:09:20,674
He was, but now I can't find him.

1113
01:09:20,675 --> 01:09:21,773
Where is he?

1114
01:09:21,857 --> 01:09:23,816
Ho ho! You won't find him here!

1115
01:09:24,958 --> 01:09:27,236
The king has returned.

1116
01:09:27,363 --> 01:09:30,531
I can't believe it. He's gone back!

1117
01:09:30,616 --> 01:09:32,450
Gone back? What do you mean?

1118
01:09:32,618 --> 01:09:35,536
Hey, what's goin' on here?

1119
01:09:35,621 --> 01:09:37,955
-Who's the monkey?
-Simba went back to challenge Scar.

1120
01:09:38,040 --> 01:09:39,073
-Who?
-Scar.

1121
01:09:39,074 --> 01:09:41,042
-Who's got a scar?
-No, it's his uncle.

1122
01:09:41,126 --> 01:09:42,877
-The monkey's his uncle?
-No!

1123
01:09:42,961 --> 01:09:46,547
Simba's gone back to challenge
his uncle to take his place as king.

1124
01:09:46,632 --> 01:09:47,924
BOTH: Oh.

1125
01:10:45,190 --> 01:10:47,191
NALA: Simba, wait up!

1126
01:10:50,779 --> 01:10:52,000
It's awful, isn't it?

1127
01:10:52,774 --> 01:10:55,324
I didn't want to believe you.

1128
01:10:55,325 --> 01:10:56,645
What made you come back?

1129
01:10:57,436 --> 01:11:00,071
I finally got some sense
knocked into me,

1130
01:11:00,072 --> 01:11:02,415
and I've got the bump to prove it.

1131
01:11:02,791 --> 01:11:05,209
Besides, this is my kingdom.

1132
01:11:05,544 --> 01:11:08,337
If I don't fight for it, who will?

1133
01:11:08,630 --> 01:11:11,424
-I will.
-It's gonna be dangerous.

1134
01:11:11,508 --> 01:11:12,929
Danger? Ha!

1135
01:11:12,930 --> 01:11:15,626
I laugh in the face of danger. Ha ha ha!

1136
01:11:15,627 --> 01:11:17,805
I see nothing funny about this.

1137
01:11:17,890 --> 01:11:20,892
Timon! Pumbaa!
What are you doing here?

1138
01:11:21,018 --> 01:11:23,144
At your service, my liege.

1139
01:11:23,228 --> 01:11:25,569
Aww! We're gonna fight your uncle

1140
01:11:25,570 --> 01:11:26,898
for this?

1141
01:11:27,357 --> 01:11:29,975
Yes, Timon. This is my home.

1142
01:11:30,536 --> 01:11:33,070
Oh. Talk about your fixer-upper!

1143
01:11:33,405 --> 01:11:34,474
Well, Simba,

1144
01:11:34,475 --> 01:11:37,264
if it's important to you,
we're with you to the end.

1145
01:11:56,428 --> 01:12:00,306
Hyenas. I hate hyenas.

1146
01:12:00,390 --> 01:12:02,850
So what's your plan
for getting past those guys?

1147
01:12:03,227 --> 01:12:06,312
-Live bait.
-Good idea. Hey!

1148
01:12:06,396 --> 01:12:09,505
Come on, Timon. You guys
have to create a diversion.

1149
01:12:09,506 --> 01:12:11,901
What do you want me to do,
dress in drag and do the hula?

1150
01:12:13,201 --> 01:12:14,068
Luau!

1151
01:12:14,069 --> 01:12:15,886
<i>♪ If you're hungry for a hunk
of fat and juicy meat ♪</i>

1152
01:12:15,887 --> 01:12:17,850
<i>♪ Eat my buddy Pumbaa here
because he is a treat ♪</i>

1153
01:12:17,851 --> 01:12:19,703
<i>♪ Come on down and dine
on this tasty swine ♪</i>

1154
01:12:19,704 --> 01:12:21,753
<i>♪ All you have to do is get in line ♪</i>

1155
01:12:21,754 --> 01:12:23,632
-Are you achin'
-Yep, yep, yep.

1156
01:12:23,633 --> 01:12:25,435
-For some bacon?
-Yep, yep, yep.

1157
01:12:25,616 --> 01:12:27,376
-He's a big pig
-Yep, yep.

1158
01:12:27,377 --> 01:12:29,444
You could be a big pig, too! Oi!

1159
01:12:34,350 --> 01:12:37,885
Nala, you find my mother
and rally the lionesses.

1160
01:12:37,970 --> 01:12:39,177
I'll look for Scar.

1161
01:12:43,008 --> 01:12:45,017
Sarabi!

1162
01:12:59,700 --> 01:13:00,908
Yes, Scar?

1163
01:13:00,993 --> 01:13:04,453
Where is your hunting party?
They're not doing their job.

1164
01:13:04,538 --> 01:13:07,665
Scar, there is no food.
The herds have moved on.

1165
01:13:07,666 --> 01:13:10,251
No, you're just not
looking hard enough.

1166
01:13:10,252 --> 01:13:14,255
It's over.
There is nothing left.

1167
01:13:14,339 --> 01:13:18,217
We have only one choice.
We must leave Pride Rock.

1168
01:13:18,343 --> 01:13:19,744
We're not going anywhere.

1169
01:13:19,745 --> 01:13:21,746
You have sentenced us to death.

1170
01:13:21,747 --> 01:13:24,015
-Then so be it.
-You can't do that.

1171
01:13:24,099 --> 01:13:26,475
I am the king. I can do whatever I want.

1172
01:13:26,476 --> 01:13:28,754
If you were half the king Mufasa was...

1173
01:13:28,755 --> 01:13:31,264
I'm ten times the king Mufasa was!

1174
01:13:34,568 --> 01:13:36,986
Mufasa? No, you're dead.

1175
01:13:44,283 --> 01:13:45,911
Mufasa?

1176
01:13:47,205 --> 01:13:49,332
No. It's me.

1177
01:13:50,083 --> 01:13:53,038
Simba! You're alive?

1178
01:13:53,595 --> 01:13:55,065
How can that be?

1179
01:13:55,066 --> 01:13:58,666
It doesn't matter.
I'm home.

1180
01:13:59,051 --> 01:14:00,154
Simba?

1181
01:14:00,469 --> 01:14:02,130
Simba!

1182
01:14:02,131 --> 01:14:05,736
Oh, I'm a little surprised
to see you

1183
01:14:05,737 --> 01:14:06,599
alive.

1184
01:14:08,226 --> 01:14:10,013
Give me one good reason

1185
01:14:10,014 --> 01:14:11,771
why I shouldn't rip you apart.

1186
01:14:11,855 --> 01:14:13,814
Oh, Simba, you must understand.

1187
01:14:13,899 --> 01:14:16,159
The pressures of ruling a kingdom...

1188
01:14:16,160 --> 01:14:19,612
Are no longer yours.
Step down, Scar.

1189
01:14:19,696 --> 01:14:22,239
Oh, well, I would, naturally.

1190
01:14:22,240 --> 01:14:25,576
However, there is one little problem.

1191
01:14:25,577 --> 01:14:27,036
You see them?

1192
01:14:28,747 --> 01:14:31,040
They think I'm king.

1193
01:14:31,124 --> 01:14:32,403
<i>Well, we don't.</i>

1194
01:14:32,760 --> 01:14:34,877
Simba's the rightful king.

1195
01:14:34,961 --> 01:14:37,254
The choice is yours, Scar.

1196
01:14:37,255 --> 01:14:38,999
Either step down or fight.

1197
01:14:39,611 --> 01:14:42,468
Oh, must this all end in violence?

1198
01:14:42,469 --> 01:14:46,263
I'd hate to be responsible
for the death of a family member.

1199
01:14:46,348 --> 01:14:49,600
-Wouldn't you agree, Simba?
-That's not gonna work, Scar.

1200
01:14:50,102 --> 01:14:51,210
I've put it behind me.

1201
01:14:51,211 --> 01:14:53,110
But what about your faithful subjects?

1202
01:14:53,111 --> 01:14:54,790
Have they put it behind them?

1203
01:14:55,273 --> 01:14:57,158
Simba, what is he talking about?

1204
01:14:57,442 --> 01:15:01,696
Ah, so you haven't told them
your little secret.

1205
01:15:01,780 --> 01:15:05,241
Well, Simba,
now's your chance to tell them.

1206
01:15:05,242 --> 01:15:09,412
Tell them who is responsible
for Mufasa's death.

1207
01:15:12,457 --> 01:15:13,344
I am.

1208
01:15:18,004 --> 01:15:20,548
It's not true.

1209
01:15:20,966 --> 01:15:23,100
Tell me it's not true.

1210
01:15:24,845 --> 01:15:25,937
It's true.

1211
01:15:25,938 --> 01:15:28,398
You see? He admits it!

1212
01:15:28,399 --> 01:15:31,183
-Murderer!
-No! It was an accident.

1213
01:15:31,184 --> 01:15:33,509
If it weren't for you,
Mufasa would still be alive.

1214
01:15:33,510 --> 01:15:34,801
It's your fault he's dead!

1215
01:15:34,802 --> 01:15:36,564
-Do you deny it?
-No.

1216
01:15:36,648 --> 01:15:38,926
Then you're guilty.

1217
01:15:38,927 --> 01:15:40,701
No, I'm not a murderer!

1218
01:15:40,702 --> 01:15:43,195
Oh, Simba, you're in trouble again,

1219
01:15:43,321 --> 01:15:46,365
but this time
daddy isn't here to save you,

1220
01:15:46,366 --> 01:15:49,660
and now everyone knows why!

1221
01:15:50,746 --> 01:15:51,829
Simba!

1222
01:15:57,419 --> 01:16:02,006
Now, this looks familiar. Hmm.

1223
01:16:02,090 --> 01:16:04,999
Where have I seen this before?
Let me think. Hmm.

1224
01:16:06,136 --> 01:16:08,763
Oh, yes. I remember.

1225
01:16:09,347 --> 01:16:13,017
This is just the way
your father looked before he died.

1226
01:16:14,895 --> 01:16:18,606
And here's my little secret.

1227
01:16:19,065 --> 01:16:22,193
I killed Mufasa.

1228
01:16:23,820 --> 01:16:26,906
No! Murderer!

1229
01:16:27,699 --> 01:16:30,159
-No, Simba, please.
-Tell them the truth.

1230
01:16:30,243 --> 01:16:33,603
Truth? But truth is in
the eye of the behold...

1231
01:16:34,414 --> 01:16:35,598
All right.

1232
01:16:36,112 --> 01:16:37,568
All right.

1233
01:16:38,794 --> 01:16:39,999
I did it.

1234
01:16:40,378 --> 01:16:42,000
So they can hear you.

1235
01:16:43,340 --> 01:16:46,209
I killed Mufasa!

1236
01:16:56,561 --> 01:16:58,604
Hee-yah!

1237
01:16:59,022 --> 01:17:01,899
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Comin' through. Hot stuff. Whoo!

1238
01:17:28,218 --> 01:17:29,718
Aagghh!

1239
01:17:31,221 --> 01:17:33,722
-Let me out! Let me out!
-Let me in! Let me in!

1240
01:17:35,479 --> 01:17:37,434
Please, don't eat me.

1241
01:17:37,519 --> 01:17:38,694
Drop 'em!

1242
01:17:39,187 --> 01:17:41,605
-Hey, who's the pig?
-Are you talkin' to me?

1243
01:17:41,606 --> 01:17:43,649
-Uh-oh. He called him a pig.
-Are you talkin' to me?

1244
01:17:43,650 --> 01:17:45,356
-Shouldn't have done that.
-Are you talkin' to me?

1245
01:17:45,469 --> 01:17:51,282
-Now they're in for it.
-They call me Mr Pig!

1246
01:17:51,533 --> 01:17:54,410
Aaaaggghhh!

1247
01:17:54,536 --> 01:17:57,204
<i>Take that, you stupid...</i>

1248
01:17:57,289 --> 01:17:59,290
<i>Take that and that!</i>

1249
01:18:02,878 --> 01:18:04,920
Run, you yellow-belly!

1250
01:18:05,088 --> 01:18:06,630
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!

1251
01:18:24,983 --> 01:18:27,818
-Murderer.
-Simba. Simba, please.

1252
01:18:27,944 --> 01:18:29,851
Please, have mercy. I beg you.

1253
01:18:29,852 --> 01:18:31,822
You don't deserve to live.

1254
01:18:31,907 --> 01:18:37,328
But Simba, I am family.

1255
01:18:37,662 --> 01:18:41,185
It's the hyenas who are the real enemy.

1256
01:18:41,186 --> 01:18:43,366
It was their fault.
It was their idea.

1257
01:18:43,367 --> 01:18:45,711
Why should I believe you?

1258
01:18:46,212 --> 01:18:48,881
Everything you ever told me was a lie.

1259
01:18:48,965 --> 01:18:50,925
What are you going to do?

1260
01:18:51,009 --> 01:18:54,595
You wouldn't kill your own uncle.

1261
01:18:55,013 --> 01:18:57,139
No, Scar.

1262
01:18:57,474 --> 01:18:59,016
I'm not like you.

1263
01:18:59,100 --> 01:19:01,375
Oh, Simba, thank you.

1264
01:19:01,376 --> 01:19:04,142
You are truly noble.
I'll make it up to you, I promise.

1265
01:19:04,143 --> 01:19:06,315
And how can I prove myself to you?

1266
01:19:06,316 --> 01:19:07,720
Tell me. I mean, anything.

1267
01:19:08,401 --> 01:19:10,027
Run.

1268
01:19:10,028 --> 01:19:12,154
Run away, Scar,

1269
01:19:12,280 --> 01:19:14,159
and never return.

1270
01:19:15,408 --> 01:19:17,409
Er... Yes.

1271
01:19:17,494 --> 01:19:19,620
Of course.

1272
01:19:19,704 --> 01:19:22,373
As you wish,

1273
01:19:22,499 --> 01:19:24,541
your Majesty!

1274
01:20:17,762 --> 01:20:21,065
Ah, my friends!

1275
01:20:21,349 --> 01:20:25,185
Friends? I thought he said
we were the enemy.

1276
01:20:25,270 --> 01:20:28,022
Yeah. That's what I heard.

1277
01:20:28,273 --> 01:20:29,606
Ed?

1278
01:20:33,653 --> 01:20:38,198
No. Let me explain.
No, you don't understand!

1279
01:20:38,283 --> 01:20:40,701
No, I didn't mean... No! No!

1280
01:21:47,102 --> 01:21:48,769
It is time.

1281
01:22:13,711 --> 01:22:16,922
MUFASA: Remember

1282
01:22:30,311 --> 01:22:32,229
Se-fi-Ie

1283
01:22:32,313 --> 01:22:34,106
Baba ti-tabo

1284
01:22:34,232 --> 01:22:37,067
Maye babo busa ilomhlaba

1285
01:22:43,283 --> 01:22:45,200
Ubuse ngo xolo

1286
01:22:45,285 --> 01:22:46,910
Ubuse ngo thando

1287
01:22:47,036 --> 01:22:48,662
Ubuse ngo xolo

1288
01:22:48,746 --> 01:22:50,664
Ubuse ngo thando

1289
01:22:50,748 --> 01:22:53,041
Ubuse ngo xolo

1290
01:22:53,126 --> 01:22:55,252
Ingonyama inengw' enamabala

1291
01:22:55,336 --> 01:22:58,380
Ingonyama nengw' enamabala

1292
01:22:58,464 --> 01:23:03,302
<i>♪ Till we find our place ♪</i>

1293
01:23:03,428 --> 01:23:08,182
<i>♪ On the path unwinding ♪</i>

1294
01:23:09,601 --> 01:23:14,563
<i>♪ In the circle ♪</i>

1295
01:23:14,647 --> 01:23:19,818
<i>♪ The circle of life ♪</i>

1296
01:23:19,944 --> 01:23:21,612
<i>♪ Circle of ♪</i>

1297
01:23:21,696 --> 01:23:23,864
<i>♪ Life ♪</i>

1298
01:24:25,393 --> 01:24:29,430
<i>♪ There's a calm surrender ♪</i>

1299
01:24:29,431 --> 01:24:33,517
<i>♪ To the rush of day ♪</i>

1300
01:24:33,518 --> 01:24:37,437
<i>♪ When the heat of a rolling wind ♪</i>

1301
01:24:37,438 --> 01:24:41,450
<i>♪ Can be turned away ♪</i>

1302
01:24:41,451 --> 01:24:45,554
<i>♪ An enchanted moment ♪</i>

1303
01:24:45,555 --> 01:24:49,500
<i>♪ And it sees me through ♪</i>

1304
01:24:49,501 --> 01:24:53,520
<i>♪ It's enough for this restless warrior ♪</i>

1305
01:24:53,521 --> 01:24:57,274
<i>♪ Just to be with you ♪</i>

1306
01:24:57,275 --> 01:25:06,016
<i>♪ And can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

1307
01:25:06,017 --> 01:25:10,505
<i>♪ It is where we are ♪</i>

1308
01:25:13,525 --> 01:25:15,651
<i>♪ It's enough ♪</i>

1309
01:25:15,652 --> 01:25:20,153
<i>♪ For this wide-eyed wanderer ♪</i>

1310
01:25:20,154 --> 01:25:25,449
<i>♪ That we got this far ♪</i>

1311
01:25:27,607 --> 01:25:36,213
<i>♪ And can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

1312
01:25:36,214 --> 01:25:40,584
<i>♪ How it's laid to rest? ♪</i>

1313
01:25:43,721 --> 01:25:45,772
<i>♪ It's enough ♪</i>

1314
01:25:45,773 --> 01:25:50,305
<i>♪ To make kings and vagabonds ♪</i>

1315
01:25:50,306 --> 01:25:55,599
<i>♪ Believe the very best ♪</i>

1316
01:26:13,293 --> 01:26:17,184
<i>♪ There's a time for everyone ♪</i>

1317
01:26:17,185 --> 01:26:21,282
<i>♪ If they only learn ♪</i>

1318
01:26:21,283 --> 01:26:25,194
<i>♪ That the twisting kaleidoscope ♪</i>

1319
01:26:25,195 --> 01:26:29,358
<i>♪ Moves us all in turn ♪</i>

1320
01:26:29,359 --> 01:26:33,248
<i>♪ There's a rhyme and reason ♪</i>

1321
01:26:33,249 --> 01:26:37,295
<i>♪ To the wild outdoors ♪</i>

1322
01:26:37,296 --> 01:26:41,226
<i>♪ When the heart
of this star-crossed voyager ♪</i>

1323
01:26:41,227 --> 01:26:47,030
<i>♪ Beats in time with yours ♪</i>

1324
01:26:47,031 --> 01:26:55,892
<i>♪ And can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

1325
01:26:55,893 --> 01:26:59,663
<i>♪ It is where we are ♪</i>

1326
01:27:03,377 --> 01:27:05,582
<i>♪ It's enough ♪</i>

1327
01:27:05,583 --> 01:27:09,869
<i>♪ For this wide-eyed wanderer ♪</i>

1328
01:27:09,870 --> 01:27:14,845
<i>♪ That we got this far ♪</i>

1329
01:27:17,048 --> 01:27:25,790
<i>♪ And can you feel the love tonight? ♪</i>

1330
01:27:25,791 --> 01:27:30,744
<i>♪ How it's laid to rest? ♪</i>

1331
01:27:33,201 --> 01:27:35,336
<i>♪ It's enough ♪</i>

1332
01:27:35,337 --> 01:27:39,594
<i>♪ To make kings and vagabonds ♪</i>

1333
01:27:39,595 --> 01:27:44,583
<i>♪ Believe the very best ♪</i>

1334
01:27:48,112 --> 01:27:50,153
<i>♪ It's enough ♪</i>

1335
01:27:50,154 --> 01:27:54,649
<i>♪ To make kings and vagabonds ♪</i>

1336
01:27:54,650 --> 01:28:03,999
<i>♪ Believe the very best ♪</i>

1337
01:28:04,000 --> 01:28:08,000


1338
01:28:08,001 --> 01:28:12,000


